<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>River levels remain higher than normal but are now falling. Flooding may affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly low-lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Drier conditions are forecast this week, and conditions will continue to improve. We are closely monitoring the situation and will issue further alerts and warnings if required. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water and consider activating any flood protection products you may have. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 18/11/2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-17T09:48:24</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible on Monday 17 November 2025, especially in the Shipton Under Wychwood Area. The forecast is for a predominantly dry day. Levels are now falling along much of the River Evenlode. Levels are stable on the River Glyme.

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 

This message will be updated by 19:00 PM on 17 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-17T08:44:25</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible on Monday 17 November 2025, especially in the Hannington area. The forecast is for a predominantly dry day. Levels are falling steadily and expected to continue falling through today.

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 19:00 PM on 17 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-17T08:39:34</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Middle Avon Rugby to Bidford</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-16T18:13:44</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise as a result of widespread heavy rainfall last Friday. Flooding may continue over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. Predicted peaks:- Mythe 4.1m to 4.2m on 17/11 AM, Haw Bridge 4.9m to 4.95m on 17/11 AM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 18 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-17T08:20:06</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Leadon catchment</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car. Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-17T08:19:46</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise as a result of widespread heavy rainfall last Friday. Flooding may continue over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubillee Bridge to Fladbury is impacted. Observed peak:- Evesham 2.4m 16/11 AM. Predicted peak:- Bredon 2.7m 17/11 AM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded.  This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 18 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-17T08:20:10</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-17T09:32:18</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-17T09:30:53</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise as a result of widespread heavy rainfall last Friday. Flooding may continue over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury, including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St Gate is closed at Upton upon Severn. Predicted peaks: - Bewdley 4.0m to 4.8m on 18/11 AM, Worcester 4.6m to 4.7m on 18/11 AM, Diglis 4.5m to 4.6m on 18/11 AM, Kempsey Yacht Club 6.6m to 6.7m on 18/11 AM, Saxons Lode 4.9m to 5.0m on 19/11 AM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 18 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-17T08:20:14</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Severn Ham, Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise as a result of widespread heavy rainfall. Flooding is expected to continue today 17 November 2025, and over the next few days.
Flooding may affect property and roads around Mill Avon Riverside including minor roads at Tirley, Chaceley, Hasfield, Hawbridge, Lower Lode, Ashleworth, Deerhurst, Wainlode and Apperley.
Predicted peak:- at Mythe 4.1m to 4.2m on 17/11 AM.
We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.
This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 18 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-17T08:16:59</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Apperley and The Leigh</title>
      <description>Rising river levels are expected to cause flooding today.
Flooding is expected to continue over the next few days.  Flooding may affect the B4213 at Haw Bridge.
Predicted peak:- Haw Bridge 4.9m to 4.95m on 17/11 AM. 
We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 
This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 18 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-17T08:16:53</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Avon at Strensham and Bredon</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car. Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-17T08:32:13</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
