<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Tidal River Avon at Bristol, Pill and Shirehampton</title>
      <description>High tides today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from 17:45 to 19:45 this evening and 06:15 to 08:15 tomorrow morning 
The detailed tidal forecast for those who use it is for a peak level at Avonmouth. The first forecast high water is at  18:45 on 05/11/2025 with a level of 7.57 mAODN with  Easterly force 4 winds. winds. The second forecast high water is at  07:15 on 06/11/2025 with a level of 7.57 mAODN with South Easterly force 3 winds. (mAODN is height above average sea level.) 
Further flooding is possible until Friday Evening due to high spring tides. 
Locations most affected will be low lying land and roads near rivers or on the coast. 
We are closing flood gates . 
Avoid coastal roads, which may be flooded . 
This message will be updated by 1:45PM on 06 November 2025 or as the situation changes.

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-05T13:54:04</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high and may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 06 November 2025. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye from Hay on Wye to Ross on Wye. Other locations affected may include the A438 between Letton &amp; Willersey, Byford, Bredwardine &amp; Hereford. Road closures &amp; diversions on the A438 may be in force. Predicted peaks:- Hay on Wye peaked at 3.0m 05/11 AM, Bredwardine peaked at 4.7m on 05/11 PM, Belmont peaked 4.8m on 05/11 PM, Old Wye Bridge peaked at 4.2m on 05/11 PM, Mordiford peaked at 4.3m on 06/11 AM, Ross on Wye 3.6m to 3.8m on 06/11 PM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 7PM on 06 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-06T08:19:12</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high and may lead to flooding.  Flooding is possible on 06 November 2025.  Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye. Predicted peaks:- Ross on Wye 3.6m to 3.8m 06/11 AM.  We are closely monitoring the situation.  Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  This message will be updated by 7PM on 06 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-06T08:21:24</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Wye Estuary in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>High tides this evening may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from 5pm today 05/11/25 and tomorrow morning from 6am, 06/11/25 
A series of high tides is due over the next few days. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the Wye Estuary from Redbrook to Chepstow. Predicted peaks:- Avonmouth Portbury 7.3m to 7.6m this evening, 05/11/25, Newport 6.9m to 7.3m this evening , 05/11/25. Tomorrow morning's high tide is forecast  between 6 and 7am, 06/11/25, predicted peaks :- Avonmouth Portbury 7.3m to 7.6m, Newport 7.1 m to 7.3m. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 06 November 2025 or as the situation changes.

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-05T16:50:37</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
