<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Tidal River Avon at Bristol, Pill and Shirehampton</title>
      <description>Higher than normal spring tides are forecast over the coming days. Flooding of roads and low-lying land is possible, property flooding is not expected.
The forecast high-water is 8:00 PM today 08/10/25 with a level of 7.72 mAOD and a Force 4 North-Westerly wind. The second forecast high-water is 8:15 AM on 09/10/25 with a level of 7.45 mAOD and a Force 2 North-Westerly wind. Times are local and refer to the high-water time at Avonmouth, mAOD is height above average sea level. Conditions may apply one to two hours either side of the high tide. 
Areas most at risk include the tidal River Avon from Sea Mills to Conham in Bristol and between the Avonmouth Bridge and Shirehampton Park including Pill and Shirehampton.
Further flooding is possible at high-water until tomorrow evening due to higher than normal tides. We are closely monitoring the situation and will be closing flood gates at Pill.
Please be careful along low-lying land near watercourses where conditions may be hazardous.
This message will be updated by 2:00 PM on 09/10/2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-10-08T12:12:11</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Wye Estuary in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>A flood alert has been issued due to a period of high tides. 
Tides will be at their highest around 21:30 this evening 09/10/25 and at 09:45 on Friday morning 10/10/25. Flooding of roads and low-lying land adjacent to the Wye Estuary from Redbrook to Chepstow is expected at the time of high tides, however conditions may apply a few hours either side of the high tides. 
Predicted peaks this evening Thursday 09/10/25: Newport 6.9m to 7.3m around 21:30 and Avonmouth 7.3m to 7.6m around 21:45. 
Predicted peaks tomorrow morning Friday 09/10/25: Newport 6.6m to 6.9m around 09:45 and Avonmouth 7.0m to 7.2m around 10:00. 
We are closely monitoring the situation. Please avoid using low lying footpaths near local watercourses. This message will be updated by 11:00 on 10/10/25, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-10-09T09:41:52</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
