<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Tidal River Avon at Bristol, Pill and Shirehampton</title>
      <description>Flooding of roads and low lying land is possible, property flooding is not expected.
Flooding is possible for a few hours either side of high water at 9:45 PM on 31/03/2025 and 10:00 AM om 01/04/2025
Areas most at risk include the tidal River Avon from Sea Mills to Conham in Bristol and between the Avonmouth Bridge and Shirehampton Park including Pill and Shirehampton.
We have closed flood gates at Pill.
Be careful along beaches, promenades, coastal footpaths and roads.
The detailed tidal forecast is for a peak level at Avonmouth. The first forecast high water is at 9:45 PM on 31/03/2025 with a level of 7.58 mAOD with south-easterly force 3 winds.  The second forecast tide is at 10:00 AM on 01/04/2025 with a level of 7.45 mAOD with easterly force 4 winds.  This Flood Alert is likely to be in force until Tuesday 1st April.
This message will be updated in the afternoon of 01/04/2025, or as the situation changes.</description>
      <pubDate>2025-03-31T16:47:05</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Severn estuary from Gloucester to Sharpness</title>
      <description> The Flood Alert for the area has now been removed.  Peak tides are now forecast to fall below the flood risk threshold.  
We continue to monitor the situation.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-04-01T11:33:41</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Wye Estuary in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description> The Flood Alert for the area has now been removed.  Peak tides are now forecast to fall below the flood risk threshold.  
We continue to monitor the situation.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-04-01T11:33:45</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Wye Estuary at Brockweir</title>
      <description> This Flood Warning has been removed.  
The Flood Warning for the area has now been removed.  However, a Flood Alert remains in force for the wider area, so flooding may still affect roads and low lying land.  
We continue to monitor the situation.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-03-31T16:24:27</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
