<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>River levels are now rising in response to heavy rainfall and are forecast to continue rising.
Flooding is possible Friday 14/11/2025 and Saturday 15/11/2025.
Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Drier conditions are forecast from Saturday and conditions will begin to improve.
We are closely monitoring the situation and will issue further alerts and warnings if required.
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water and consider activating any flood protection products you may have.
This message will be updated by 2:00PM on 15/11/2025 or as the situation changes.

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-14T13:53:26</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible today (15/11/25) especially in the Cerney Wick area. Today will be mostly dry but with some rain possible later. We expect river levels to rise until tomorrow 16/11/25. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Don't put yourself or others at risk. 

This message will be updated by 20:00, 15 November 2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T08:22:47</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>"Rising river levels may lead to continued flooding.  

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible on the 15th November 2025, especially in the Shipton Under Wychwood Area.  Today will be mostly dry but with some rain possible later.

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 

This message will be updated by 20:00, 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T07:29:47</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>Flooding of low-lying land and roads remains possible on 15th November 2025. Today will be mostly dry but with some rain possible later. We expect river levels to remain high on 15 November 2025. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to river levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 20:00, 15 November 2025, or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T08:11:44</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Tributaries on the Upper River Thames above Cricklade</title>
      <description>"High river levels may lead to flooding.

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible, especially in the Purton Stoke and Swill Brook areas. Today will be mostly dry but with some rain possible later.. We expect river levels to drop over the weekend. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 

This message will be updated by 20:00 15 Nov 2025 or as the situation changes."
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T07:30:20</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Middle Avon Rugby to Bidford</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 15 November 2025. Flooding may affect low-lying land and roads adjacent to the River Avon between Rugby and Bidford including Warwick, Stratford upon Avon, caravan parks and farmland. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T07:46:38</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Tributaries in Gloucester</title>
      <description>Widespread heavy rainfall throughout today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 14th November 2025 and over the weekend.
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to Horsbere Brook, Wotton Brook, River Twyver, River Sud, Whaddon Brook, Daniels Brook &amp; Dimore Brook. Locations that may be affected include Kemerton, Tewkesbury, Stoke Orchard, Uckington, Churchdown, Upton St Leonards, Cheltenham, Horsebere and Brookthorpe. The Horsbere flood storage area may be operating. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-14T09:18:05</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Stour in South Warwickshire</title>
      <description>Forecast high river levels today may lead to flooding. 

Flooding is possible from the morning of 14 November 2025.

Flooding may affect low lying land and roads around Shipston on Stour, Tredington, Halford, Newbold on Stour, Crimscote, Wimpstone and Clifford Chambers.

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.

This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-14T08:09:26</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Rivers Frome and Cam</title>
      <description>Forecast rising river levels today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible on 14 November 2025 and over the next few days 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the river from Elmore to Sharpness. Other locations that may be affected include Chalford, Leonard Stanley and Cambridge. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-14T15:58:38</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Little Avon catchment and the Vale of Berkeley</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible on 14 November 2025 . 
Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Little Avon, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected. Areas most at risk include the Little Avon River and other rivers and streams in the Vale of Berkeley. Drier conditions are forecast from Saturday and conditions will begin to improve. 
We are closely monitoring the situation and will issue further alerts and warnings if required. 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water water and consider activating any flood protection products you may have. 
This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-14T16:06:14</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Rivers in South Worcestershire</title>
      <description>Widespread heavy rainfall throughout today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 14th November 2025 and over the weekend.
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the river from North Littleton to Winchcombe. Other locations that may be affected are Badsey, Childswickham, Broadway, Sedgeberrow, Toddington and the Road at Hinton on the Green bridge. This alert has been issued based on uncertain forecast heavy rainfall that may have significant impact within the community. As the worst of the rain has not yet fallen we are unable to provide any real time peak information. As the situation evolves we will be able to provide more details. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and void low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-14T09:04:26</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Tributaries in Cheltenham and Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>Widespread heavy rainfall throughout today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 14th November 2025 and over the weekend. 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to Wymans Brook, Carrant Brook, Hatherley Brook, Swilgate and the River Chelt. Locations that may be affected include Mitton, Ashchurch, Walton Cardiff and locations along the River Chelt from Charlton Kings to Uckington and Boddington. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-14T09:12:26</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>Widespread heavy rainfall throughout today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 14th November 2025 and over the weekend. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. This alert has been issued based on uncertain forecast heavy rainfall that may have significant impact within the community. As the worst of the rain has not yet fallen we are unable to provide any real time peak information.  As the situation evolves we will be able to provide more details. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-14T09:09:58</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leadon catchment</title>
      <description>River levels remain high as a result of widespread heavy rain. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the River Leadon. Locations that may be affected include Ledbury, Much Marcle, Staunton, Tibberton and Wedderburn Bridge may now be impassable. Water is over the road at Upleadon Court. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded.  This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T09:41:31</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise as a result of widespread heavy rainfall. Flooding may continue over the weekend. 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubillee Bridge to Fladbury is impacted. Predicted peaks:- Evesham 2.5m to 2.9m on 15/11 night, Bredon 2.2m to 2.7m on 16/11 PM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 
This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T09:09:10</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Bristol Frome catchment</title>
      <description>Rising river levels today may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible on 14 November 2025 . 
Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Frome, Bristol Floating Harbour, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected.  Areas most at risk include St John's Way in Chipping Sodbury and Damson Bridge. Drier conditions are forecast from Saturday and conditions will begin to improve. 
We are closely monitoring the situation and will issue further alerts and warnings if required. 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water and consider activating any flood protection products you may have. 
This message will be updated by 12:00PM on 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-14T15:37:13</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Bristol Frome from downstream of Nibley to Stapleton</title>
      <description>The Flood Warning has now been removed. However, a Flood Alert remains in force for the wider area, so flooding of roads and low lying land is still possible. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T10:31:56</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>High river levels may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 15 November 2025. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye from Hay on Wye to Ross on Wye. Other locations affected may include the A438 between Letton &amp; Willersey, Byford, Bredwardine &amp; Hereford. Road closures &amp; diversions on the A438 may be in force. Predicted peaks:- Bredwardine 4.6m to 4.8m on Saturday15/11 AM, Old Wye Bridge 4m to 4.3m on 15/11 PM, Ross on Wye 3m to 3.4 on 16/11 PM. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T07:46:38</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Rivers in the Forest of Dean</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding.

Flooding is possible on 15th November 2025 and over the weekend.

Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the river from Gloucester to Chepstow. Other locations that may be affected include Westbury and Lydney. 

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 

This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T05:21:59</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>Forecast rising river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 15 November 2025. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye. Predicted peaks:- Ross on Wye 3.6m to 4.1m on 16/11 AM.  Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T09:02:00</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise as a result of widespread heavy rainfall. Flooding may continue over the weekend. Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury; including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St Gate is closed at Upton upon Severn. Predicted peaks:- Bewdley 4.60m to 5.10m on 17/11 PM, Worcester 4.10m to 4.60m on 17/11 night, Diglis 3.90m to 4.40m on 17/11 night, Kempsey Yacht Club 5.80m to 6.20m on 16/11 night, Saxons Lode 4.50m to 4.90m on 17/11 AM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T09:18:22</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Severn Ham, Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>Rising river levels are expected to cause flooding overnight. 
Flooding is expected on 14 November 2025 and the next few days 
Flooding may affect property and roads around Mill Avon Riverside including minor roads at Tirley, Chaceley, Hasfield, Hawbridge, Lower Lode, Ashleworth, Deerhurst, Wainlode and Apperley. Predicted peaks:- at Mythe 4.5m to 5.0m on sunday 16 November. 
We are closely monitoring the situation  
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes. 
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-14T20:08:36</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Lower Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>Flooding is expected on 15 November 2025. 
River levels remain high but have stabilised and are expected to fall through the afternoon on Saturday 15/11/2025.
Areas most at risk include low lying land at Hanham Lock and the floodplain upstream of Bath.
Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Broadmead Brook, River Boyd, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly around Areas most at risk include low lying land at Hanham Lock and the floodplain upstream of Bath. Drier conditions are forecast in the coming days and conditions are expected to continue to improve. 
We are monitoring rainfall and river levels. 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 
This message will be updated by 6:00PM on 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T10:14:38</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Avon at Strensham and Bredon</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise as a result of widespread heavy rainfall. Flooding is expected to continue over the next few days.  

Flooding may affect properties and roads around Mill Lane, Strensham and areas around Dock Lane Bredon. 

Predicted peak:- Evesham 2.5m to 2.9m overnight 15/11, Bredon 2.2 to 2.7m on 16/11 PM. 

We are closely monitoring the situation and liaising with emergency services and local authorities.  

Start acting on your flood plan if you have one and activate any flood protection products you may have. 

This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T09:15:53</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Boyd at Wick</title>
      <description>The Flood Warning has now been removed. However, a Flood Alert remains in force for the wider area, so flooding of roads and low lying land is still possible. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T08:45:40</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Bristol Frome at Chipping Sodbury and Yate, Vayre Close, Manor Way, Celestine Road and Nibley Lane</title>
      <description>The Flood Warning has now been removed. However, a Flood Alert remains in force for the wider area, so flooding of roads and low lying land is still possible. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T10:19:24</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Avon at Twyning</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise as a result of widespread heavy rainfall. Flooding is expected to continue over the next few days.  

Flooding may affect properties and roads around Twyning Green. 

Predicted peak:- Bredon 2.2m to 2.7m on 16/11 PM. 

We are closely monitoring the situation.  

Activate any flood protection products you may have. Start acting on your flood plan if you have one. 

This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T09:07:12</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: Horesbere Brook at Gloucester</title>
      <description>Rising river levels are expected to cause flooding today. 
Flooding is expected on 14 November 2025 Flooding is expected over the next few days 
Flooding may affect Properties around Park Avenue, Cypress Gardens, Greyhound Gardens, Liddington Road and Cheltenham Road Gloucester. 
We are monitoring rainfall and river levels . 
Monitor local water levels and weather conditions .Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes. 
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-14T16:31:30</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: Nailsworth Stream from Nailsworth to Dudbridge</title>
      <description>Rising river levels are expected to cause flooding this evening. 
Flooding is expected on 14 November 2025 . Flooding is expected over the next few days. 
Flooding may affect properties and roads around Brookside Cottages, Inchbrook. If levels continue to rise other locations that could be affected are George Street, Fountain Street and the A46. 
We are monitoring rainfall and river levels . 
Avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded . Don't put yourself or others at risk 
This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes. 
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-14T19:39:26</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: Daniels Brook at Lower Tuffley</title>
      <description>Rising river levels are expected to cause flooding today. 
Flooding is expected on 14 November 2025 and over the next few days 
Flooding may affect properties and roads around Charlecote Avenue, Thoresby Avenue, Boadiam Avenue and Greenhill Drive. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 15 November 2025 or as the situation changes. 
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-14T16:32:49</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
