<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>River levels remain high but are now falling in the upper catchment. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Drier conditions are forecast from today onwards and conditions will continue to improve. We are closely monitoring the situation and will issue further alerts and warnings if required. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water and consider activating any flood protection products you may have. This message will be updated by 6:00PM on 16/11/2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-16T08:04:22</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Churn and its tributaries</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T19:55:51</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>"  

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible on 16 November 2025, especially in the Shipton Under Wychwood Area. The forecast is for a predominantly dry day today. Levels are now falling along much of the River Evenlode. Levels are stable on the River Glyme.

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 

This message will be updated by 19:00 16 November 2025 or as the situation change"
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-16T08:44:00</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Thames and its small tributaries from Calcutt to Lechlade</title>
      <description>"

Flooding of low lying land and roads is possible on 16 November 2025, especially in the Hannington area. The forecast is for a predominantly dry day today. Levels are expected to stabilise today, but will remain high throughout the day.

We are closely monitoring the situation. 

Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses. Go to River levels online for updates on current river levels.

This message will be updated by 19:00 16 November 2025 or as the situation change"
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-16T08:47:18</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Dikler from Condicote to Little Rissington</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected. The forecast is for a predominantly dry day today. Levels are expected to continue dropping through today 
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-16T08:44:45</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Tributaries on the Upper River Thames above Cricklade</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected. The forecast is for a predominantly dry day today. Levels are expected to continue dropping through today. 
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-16T08:43:34</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Middle Avon Rugby to Bidford</title>
      <description>High river levels today may lead to flooding. Flooding is possible on 15 November 2025. Flooding may affect low-lying land and roads adjacent to the River Avon between Rugby and Bidford including Warwick, Stratford upon Avon, caravan parks and farmland. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T07:46:38</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Tributaries in Gloucester</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T11:17:31</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Stour in South Warwickshire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
If you have been evacuated only return to your property once the emergency services have advised that it is safe to do so. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T11:49:00</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Rivers Frome and Cam</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T11:44:02</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Little Avon catchment and the Vale of Berkeley</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain.

Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.

We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.

Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water, just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T14:54:45</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Rivers in South Worcestershire</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T11:42:57</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Tributaries in Cheltenham and Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T11:40:04</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise as a result of widespread heavy rainfall. Flooding is expected to continue over the weekend. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Severn from Tewkesbury to Gloucester. Locations that may be affected include Apperley, Maisemore, Hempstead, Minsterworth Ham and Quedgley. Severn Ham, Tewkesbury starts to fill. Predicted peaks:- Mythe 3.7m to 4.2m on 16/11 PM, Haw Bridge 4.5m to 5.0m on 19/11 PM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T15:01:40</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Leadon catchment</title>
      <description>River levels remain high as a result of widespread heavy rain. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent to the River Leadon. Locations that may be affected include Ledbury, Much Marcle, Staunton, Tibberton and Wedderburn Bridge may now be impassable. Water is over the road at Upleadon Court. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded.  This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T09:41:31</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Avon in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise as a result of widespread heavy rainfall. Flooding may continue over the weekend. 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads adjacent the River Avon from Abbotts Salford to Tewkesbury. Other locations that may be affected include Offenham, Evesham, Twyning and the Eckington Road. Mill Bank Road from Jubillee Bridge to Fladbury is impacted. Predicted peaks:- Evesham 2.5m to 2.9m on 15/11 night, Bredon 2.2m to 2.7m on 16/11 PM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and avoid low lying roads near rivers, which may be flooded. 
This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T09:09:10</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Bristol Frome catchment</title>
      <description>Flood alert no longer in force: Bristol Frome catchment

The situation is improving and no further flooding is expected in this area.

Flood warnings and alerts may still be in force for surrounding areas.

There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain.

Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.

We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.

Never drive through flood water, just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car. Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T14:52:55</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Bristol Frome from downstream of Nibley to Stapleton</title>
      <description>The Flood Warning has now been removed. However, a Flood Alert remains in force for the wider area, so flooding of roads and low lying land is still possible. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T10:31:56</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high and the potential for flooding continues today, 16 November 2025. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye from Hay on Wye to Ross on Wye. Other locations affected may include the A438 between Letton &amp; Willersey, Byford, Bredwardine &amp; Hereford. Road closures &amp; diversions on the A438 may be in force. Observed peaks:- Bredwardine 4.67m 15/11 PM, Old Wye Bridge 4.18m 15/11 PM, Hay-on-Wye 2.58m 15/11 AM, Belmont 4.8m 15/11 PM, Mordiford 4.59m 15/11 PM. Predicted peaks:- Ross on Wye 3.8m to 4.2m 16/11 AM. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 17 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-16T07:51:45</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Rivers in the Forest of Dean</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T12:24:44</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>River levels remain high and the potential for flooding continues today, 16 November 2025. Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye. Observed peaks:- Hay-on-Wye 2.58m 15/11 AM. Predicted peaks:- Ross on Wye 3.8m to 4.2m 16/11 AM. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 17 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-16T07:44:48</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Severn in Worcestershire</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise as a result of widespread heavy rainfall. Flooding may continue over the weekend. Flooding may affect low lying land &amp; roads adjacent to the river from Highley to Tewkesbury; including Dog Lane Bewdley, Stourport, Diglis &amp; Hylton Road towpath. Flooded drains affect the racecourse &amp; Worcester CCG. PLP should be installed. New St Gate is closed at Upton upon Severn. Predicted peaks:- Bewdley 3.70m to 4.20m on 17/11 PM, Worcester 4.20m to 4.70m on 18/11 AM, Diglis 4.0m to 4.40m on 18/11 AM, Kempsey Yacht Club 6.0m to 6.40m on 18/11 AM, Saxons Lode 4.30m to 4.80m on 19/11 AM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water.  This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T15:01:33</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Severn Ham, Tewkesbury</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise as a result of widespread heavy rainfall. Flooding is expected to continue over the weekend. Flooding may affect property and roads around Mill Avon Riverside including minor roads at Tirley, Chaceley, Hasfield, Hawbridge, Lower Lode, Ashleworth, Deerhurst, Wainlode and Apperley. Predicted peaks:- at Mythe 3.7m to 4.2m on 16/11 PM. We are closely monitoring the situation. Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T14:49:42</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Severn at Apperley and The Leigh</title>
      <description>Rising river levels are expected to cause flooding today. 
Flooding is expected on 15 November 2025 Flooding is expected to continue over the weekend 
Flooding may affect the B4213 at Haw Bridge. Predicted peak at Haw Bridge 4.5m to 5m on 19/11 PM. 
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 11:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes. 
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T14:35:38</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Lower Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain.

Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.

We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.

Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water, just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T14:59:14</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood warning: River Avon at Strensham and Bredon</title>
      <description>River levels continue to rise as a result of widespread heavy rainfall. Flooding is expected to continue over the next few days.  

Flooding may affect properties and roads around Mill Lane, Strensham and areas around Dock Lane Bredon. 

Predicted peak:- Evesham 2.5m to 2.9m overnight 15/11, Bredon 2.2 to 2.7m on 16/11 PM. 

We are closely monitoring the situation and liaising with emergency services and local authorities.  

Start acting on your flood plan if you have one and activate any flood protection products you may have. 

This message will be updated by 10:00AM on 16 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T09:15:53</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Bristol Frome at Chipping Sodbury and Yate, Vayre Close, Manor Way, Celestine Road and Nibley Lane</title>
      <description>The Flood Warning has now been removed. However, a Flood Alert remains in force for the wider area, so flooding of roads and low lying land is still possible. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T10:19:24</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Avon at Twyning</title>
      <description>The Flood Warning has now been removed. However, a Flood Alert remains in force for the wider area, so flooding of roads and low lying land is still possible. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T14:42:09</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Horesbere Brook at Gloucester</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T11:45:13</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Nailsworth Stream from Nailsworth to Dudbridge</title>
      <description>The Flood Warning has now been removed. However, a Flood Alert remains in force for the wider area, so flooding of roads and low lying land is still possible. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.  
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.  
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.  

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T10:51:52</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Daniels Brook at Lower Tuffley</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Weather conditions are expected to improve and no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.  
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Never drive through flood water,  just 30cm of fast flowing water is enough to move your car.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-15T10:58:56</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
