<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Flood Warnings</title>
    <link>https://environment.data.gov.uk/flood-monitoring/id/floods</link>
    <description>Current flood warnings for Gloucestershire</description>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: Upper Bristol Avon area</title>
      <description>Flooding is possible through Wednesday and Thursday as river levels continue to rise due to heavy rainfall overnight and continuing lighter rainfall today. Flooding is forecast to affect locations near the Bristol Avon, Tetbury Avon, Sherston Avon, Dauntsey Brook, with low lying land and roads expected to be most affected, particularly low lying areas in Tetbury, Badminton, Brook End at Luckington, Corsham, Lacock and the road at Reybridge. Further rain is forecast through to Saturday and levels are expected to continue rising. We are monitoring rainfall and river levels and will issue further alerts and warnings if required. Avoid using low lying footpaths and any bridges near local watercourses and consider activating any flood protection products you may have. This message will be updated by 4:00PM on 13/11/2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-12T12:46:32</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: River Evenlode from Moreton in Marsh to Cassington and also the River Glyme at Wootton and Woodstock</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Further rainfall is forecast but no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-12T09:15:45</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warning no longer in force: Tributaries on the Upper River Thames above Cricklade</title>
      <description>There is no longer a threat of flooding, though standing water and debris may still remain. 
Further rainfall is forecast but no further flooding is expected.   
We will continue to monitor the situation and will issue further alerts or warnings if necessary.   
Continue to take care on waterside roads and footpaths and don't put yourself in unnecessary danger. Stay away from floodwater - it contains hidden dangers such as open manhole covers, sewage and chemicals.   

</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-12T09:15:35</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Herefordshire</title>
      <description>Forecast rising river levels may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from 12 November 2025. 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye from Hay on Wye to Ross on Wye. Other locations affected may include the A438 between Letton &amp; Willersey, Byford, Bredwardine &amp; Hereford. Road closures &amp; diversions on the A438 may be in force. Predicted peaks:- Hay on Wye 1.7m to 2.1m on 13/11 AM, second peak Saturday, Bredwardine 3.0m to 3.5m on 13/11 AM, second peak Saturday, Belmont 3.3m to 3.6m on 13/11 AM, second peak Saturday, Old Wye Bridge 2.9m to 3.2m on 13/11 AM, second peak Saturday, Mordiford 3.3m to 3.7m on 13/11 AM, second peak Saturday, Ross on Wye 3.4m to 3.7m on 13/11PM, second peak Saturday or Sunday.
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water. 
This message will be updated by 7:00PM on 12 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-12T07:41:26</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood alert: River Wye in Gloucestershire</title>
      <description>Forecast rising river levels may lead to flooding. 
Flooding is possible from 12 November 2025. 
Flooding may affect low lying land and roads along the River Wye. Predicted peaks:- Ross on Wye 3.4m to 3.7m 13/11 PM, second peak Saturday or Sunday, Lydbrook 4.1m to 4.3m 13/11 PM, second peak Sunday.
We are closely monitoring the situation . 
Take care and avoid walking, cycling or driving through flood water . 
This message will be updated by 7:00PM on 12 November 2025 or as the situation changes.
</description>
      <pubDate>2025-11-12T07:44:33</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
