<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Metal Spike Protruding, 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8106106</link>
<description>There&amp;#39;s a metal spike - about 5cm, quite sharp, but bent almost parallel to the pavement, a couple of metres nefore car park entrance, from Pump Room direction.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Albemarle Gate, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8106106&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8106106</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:19:17 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.911467 -2.070887</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The westbound tarmac where Charlton Lane meets Old Bath Road has been cratered for a 5m stretch up to the junction. Too rough to ride on for a cycle. Road is closed 15 Sept. Add this to list., 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8106031</link>
<description>Outside 81 &amp;amp; 83 Charlton Lane on Westbound road up to junction with Old Bath Road&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8106031.0.jpeg?264b738c&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 81, Charlton Lane, Naunton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8106031&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8106031</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:53:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.880309 -2.070231</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>5 m stretch of tarmac surface has been stripped. Leading to potholes in Eastbound road outside 14 Greenhills Road entrance. Two pathetic repairs done on 21 Feb 2025 and 24 Feb 2025. Long history of inadequate patching. The westbound road opposite now has a 5 foot patch of stripped surface. Road is closed on 15. Sept. These must be fixed properly then., 2nd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8106026</link>
<description>Eastbound- entrance to 14 Greenhills Road. Westbound- on opposite side.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8106026.0.jpeg?7ed68f32&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 13, Greenhills Road, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8106026&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8106026</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:43:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.881064 -2.06537</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light on Pittville Circus stopped working a few days ago. It’s the one on Tresmere side of Circus. It’s very dark at night making walking on the pavement dangerous., 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105865</link>
<description>Pittville Circus - Tresmere side.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Pittville Circus, Ewens Farm, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105865&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105865</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:30:50 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.90447 -2.065422</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Roundabout vandalised, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105860</link>
<description>This roundabout, and another towards Woodmancote, has been vandalised as part of a campaign by an anti-immigration group. It needs to be repainted and the group invoiced for the cost of repair.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cheltenham Road, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105860&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road markings, lines and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105860</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:30:42 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.946591 -2.063904</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light not working, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105718</link>
<description>Corner of Priory Lane/Station Road junction, Bishop’s Cleeve.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 39, Priory Lane, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105718&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105718</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 22:37:08 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.947981 -2.054149</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Big flags not secure on lamposts causing distraction and danger to drivers, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105431</link>
<description>There are big flags which have been put up by amateurs on the flag posts. They won&amp;#39;t be properly secured and in the current weather could easily come down and block windscreens. They are also illegal roadside advertising and distracting for drivers.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Tewkesbury Road, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105431&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Illegal sign</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105431</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 20:46:59 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.917269 -2.106483</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large pothole in the road, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105265</link>
<description>A few feet into Alma Road when turning from the Hatherley Road. This was first reported well over 12 months ago, nothing has been done and it is becoming more and more of an issue. I watched today as several vehicles pulled into the opposite lane to avoid it. It is hazardous to drive over and hazardous to avoid. Something needs to be done.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 2, Alma Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105265&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105265</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 20:00:30 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.89053 -2.104728</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Any amount of rain causing large pool of water, pedestrians then splashed by passing cars, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105165</link>
<description>When there is any amount of rain a large amount of water pools at the junction right by the pedestrian traffic lights. There is nowhere else for pedestrians to stand and nowhere else for the cars travelling toward Cheltenham on Cheltenham Road East to go. This results in pedestrians getting soaked by passing cars while waiting to safely cross to road toward Hare and Hounds. This issue has existed since the works for the cycle path.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 2-4, Cheltenham Road East, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105165&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105165</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 19:39:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.888346 -2.186127</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Increase in dog fouling incidents - Salvia Close, Wisteria Way, Cheltenham Road East, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105144</link>
<description>There has been an increase in the number of dog fouling in the area of Salvia Close and the paths that lead toward Wisteria Way and Cheltenham Road East. Do not expect any immediate action from this report, this is more to make the council aware.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Salvia Close, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105144&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Dog fouling</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105144</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 19:32:20 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.886842 -2.190042</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Shaw Green Lane has a very uneven road surface. Potholes recur and need repair on a regular basis. Please can the Lane be resurfaced. It has not been resurfaced in 30 years. The surface resembles a patchwork quilt. A local taxi driver expressed concerns about driving on the lane and potential damage to his car. We live with it every day., 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105084</link>
<description>Shaw Green Lane from junction with Bowbridge Lane up to beyond the last house on the rhs towards Southam Lane.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 81, Shaw Green Lane, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105084&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8105084</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 22:20:58 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.917505 -2.042583</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Union flag hung from lamppost, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104817</link>
<description>On the corner between the bus stop and 1Triscombe Way, someone has attached a Union flag to the lamppost.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Triscombe Way, Golden Valley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104817&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flyposting</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104817</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:19:34 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.90901 -2.123565</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The barrier that’s been left behind caused me to crash my bicycle, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104770</link>
<description>At the intersection of Bafford Grove and Bafford Approach where a pothole had been fixed. Riding today and taking a left into Bafford Grove me handlebar snagged the barrier and I was thrown from the bike. The barrier seems to have been in place for a long time and I wasn’t travelling at speed, but none the less it had now caused me to fall off my bike.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 26, Bafford Grove, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104770&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs &amp; Barriers left behind by Contractor</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104770</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:10:12 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.878298 -2.061545</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Barrier around pothole caused me to crash, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104737</link>
<description>On the intersection of Bafford Grove and Bafford Apprach where a pothole has been fixed (I think) and the barrier has been left in place.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 26, Bafford Grove, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104737&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs &amp; Barriers left behind by Contractor</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104737</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:05:12 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.878298 -2.061545</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bank on pavement (Highways) side has completely eroded and fallen into the stream. This has been reported previously and we got an email back from Nicky Kelly about Riparian Rights, Hiwever you cannot reply to those emails and then the case gets closed. The damaged is on the Highways side and as you can see the other side the responsibility of the home owner is well maintained. There is a steep drop into the stream and Highways should visit and decide how to fix. Highways did put slabs on the Highways side at the next property along (Brenzett) a few years ago, so they clearly thought it was their responsibility then. If you reply by email, please provide a contact name number or email we can respond to if needed., 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104636</link>
<description>See what 3 words on photo. Spring Cottage, New Toad, Southam, Cheltenham GL523NX&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8104636.0.jpeg?60962110&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): New Road, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104636&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104636</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:44:28 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.93085 -2.040612</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cone left, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104497</link>
<description>They picked up the road sign but left the cone right beside it...&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8104497.0.jpeg?65d75f46&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 228, Old Bath Road, Leckhampton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104497&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs &amp; Barriers left behind by Contractor</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104497</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:15:03 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.878147 -2.070909</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lots of debris on the cycle path (gravel/leaves etc), 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104005</link>
<description>The section of the new cycle path along Evesham Road has a lot of leaves/gravel between Hill Court Road and the northern end at Racecourse roundabout. Needs regular sweeping&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Evesham Road, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104005&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8104005</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 15:55:57 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.914796 -2.069892</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hanging branches frequently get knocked off by passing high vehicles or fall during high winds. Not only is there no pavement in this area, a regularly used footpath from Byfield Close emerges onto Gambles Lane at this point and there is no option but to walk in the road. Should branch(es) fall, serious damage could be caused to passing pedestrians (many of whom are schoolchildren) or vehicles. Furthermore, although I have always picked up and disposed (recycled) fallen branches, in my mid-80s I am less inclined or able to do this. In my view, serious consideration needs to be given as to whether this particular tree is appropriate for this location., 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8103976</link>
<description>On the elevated grass bank opposite Woodmancote Farm, Gambles Lane.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8103976.0.jpeg?43ecdd60&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Gambles Lane, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8103976&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree overhanging/overgrown limb</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8103976</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 15:53:16 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.94074 -2.042824</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Path ends abruptly, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8103719</link>
<description>I did report this recently but have had no response and the iicon on the map looks to have disapeared. the prow on tommy lane ends abruptly meaning I must retrace my steps - the path seems rather pointless if you excuse the pun. can I enter the wider park area here, or elsewhere along Tommy lane to enjoy my mid-morning stroll with the hound? regards Artemey Jarre&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Tommy Taylors Lane, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8103719&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Path/Way doesn&#39;t match map</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8103719</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 15:20:57 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.912235 -2.078434</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>TMC - Defects - Other FW6  Surface problem, 1st September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8103827</link>
<description>Road closure  28 day please   tarmac patch 10000x700x30 mm footway abrupt level different stats required opposite number 1 (FW6 Abrupt Level Differences)&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8103827&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>TMC - Defects - Other FW6  Surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8103827</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 15:20:30 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.9030347 -2.07425229999998</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>