<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Manhole cover sinking, 10th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278693</link>
<description>Manhole cover on junction of church road and shurdington road has sunk an inch or two over recent weeks. Sufficient that I now actively avoid driving over it.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Shurdington Road, Shurdington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278693&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278693</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 12:42:52 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.867771 -2.111805</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>No timetables on new Bus Stops., 10th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278641</link>
<description>New bus stops to left of Sunnyfield Lane on main road are much better and in a much safer location than old one&amp;#39;s to right of Roundabout at Cold Pool Lane. Old stops in unsafe location have been removed but some 97 and 98 Stagecoach buses still stopping at old location. New stop has had timetable boards put up for one month now but still no timetables on them, leading to confusion for passengers and bus Driver&amp;#39;s alike. Contacted Stagecoach Customer services yesterday, who&amp;#39;s call centre is in Scotland, and they do not have access to mapping system&amp;#39;s to pinpoint location, despite Postcode and name of location being given, as not a timing point and, therefore, not on Driver Duty boards. They state it is County Council responsibility to place timetables. Please get this sorted if you wish public to make use of, much better, service&amp;#39;s, particularly for many elderly residents of Sunnyfield Lane.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8278641.0.jpeg?0b9a0c46&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cold Pool Lane, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278641&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Bus stop/shelter issue</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278641</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 12:32:34 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.884947 -2.12527</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potholes and degradation of road surface along entirety of Park Lane. Shoddy patching work earlier this year a compete waste of taxpayer money! Repairs urgently needed, 10th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278529</link>
<description>Entirety of Park Lane affected. Proper patching required.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Park Lane, Sevenhampton, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278529&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278529</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 12:08:14 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.900039 -1.960623</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned traffic lights and signs., 10th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278366</link>
<description>Lobleys Drive Abbeymead No reason whatsoever for temp traffic lights to be in situ.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;No work going on, road is not dug up nor is the pavement, just temp lights and abandoned orange barriers on the highway. No one whatsoever on site doing any sort of work&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please ask the contractor to collect their stuff by close of play today.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8278366.0.jpeg?4accf638&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lobleys Drive, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278366&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned materials</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278366</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:48:13 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.846123 -2.186606</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lights in the Garden do not work, 10th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278282</link>
<description>Following work on the pelican crossing the lights in the community garden no longer light up. This area has a lot of youth and public activity&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 25, Church Road, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278282&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278282</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:35:05 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.947279 -2.06083</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pile of rubbish, 10th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278228</link>
<description>Please remove this pile of rubbish from the car park by the Greyhound pub in Cheltenham Road/Greyhound gardens Longlevens.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It is in the car park, by the bushes near the electric recharging station.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Greyhound Gardens, Elmbridge, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278228&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping (not witnessed and no evidence likely)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8278228</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:28:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.877409 -2.203913</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Street light is permanently out problem, 10th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8277838</link>
<description>Gloucester Police have a contractor installing cameras and the following column has no power to it&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8277838&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8277838</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:05:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.848249 -2.174244</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ringway barriers on the pavement, 10th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8277613</link>
<description>It appears that a section of the pavement in Wellington Square has been resurfaced (which is much appreciated) but the barriers have been left by Ringway for several weeks. I know there are tree roots which are causing the surface to be raised, so if there is additional work to be done here that is good - but if not please get the barriers removed as they are blocking the pavement.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Wellington Square, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8277613&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs &amp; Barriers left behind by Contractor</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8277613</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:56:17 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.907282 -2.072152</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The signpost is loose in the pavement &amp; leaning. It could fall on a passing pedestrian., 10th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8277351</link>
<description>It is at the junction of Parabola Lane and Overton Road, on the edge of the pavement.It is a signpost regarding parking restrictions. The issue was reported to you via phone around a month ago.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Parabola Lane, Montpellier, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8277351&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Bollard leaning slightly (less than 20 degrees) (Non illuminating bollard or post)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8277351</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:21:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.898113 -2.08592</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subsidence affecting road and pavement, 10th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8277197</link>
<description>Road outside &amp;quot;Browbridge&amp;quot; house just uphill of railway bridge.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8277197.0.jpeg?60081d16&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Pirton Lane, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8277197&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8277197</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:00:42 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.878511 -2.176389</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Walk way an lake, 10th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8276797</link>
<description>I notice the fence for Brightlands Day Nursery 107 St George&amp;#39;s Rd, Cheltenham GL50 3ED None reported the bushes&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Same as Waitrose &amp;amp; Partners Cheltenham Honeybourne Way, Cheltenham GL50 3QW&amp;#10;&amp;#10;At the walk way I notice underage Teenager coming out late. Unattended without an family members. You allowed them in relationship start having sex underage going school. They understand to use adult male as Child Molester an if hate them judge speak in mind calling rapist if fear for they life an imagine die in the worst way pain suffer torture. They find vagina made them an Victim by the male got to try. She find stealing from supermarket an find prostitute sell are give up for free. She find stealing in Attempted Murder rape Child Molester an i suspect close family grow up with brother sister cousin. By they parents not strict give them so much time Unattended in the houses. Trying sex she run out to Stranger if notice take Virginity an hide if can gets pregnant. Please secured the environment. If not working 24/7 call the emergency services an alert. All out of sight parks bushes that is not fence off. Who you wants to blame.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Walk pass an see them have Tents ⛺️ can you tell if underage Teenager doing the same late at night parents pretend strict so the child hiding behind an let them out in public to blame government majesty parents make your kids do the same. If destroy they life not strict. They living under Queen Elizabeth II an King Philip Law Criticize why they kids live the best life an none gets the 3 life sentence an hold the secret for permanent made something as an little insect affect them an blame it for the law do not wants them to tell the truth. Wants them to use addiction drink Alcohol Crack Cocaine sell vagina do prostitution set up male. Wear makeup hide identity try make them feel horny dress sexy wearing leggings tin split dress half naked clothes. Tease them to Attempted find spite hate them think about rape not kill damage if so an little insect in they body affect them so they hold it against an pretend call the police cry show sad made notice face expression an find can put them in jail mental health test if can gets accident injury damage face brain body penis vagina an hide a little insect blame in the law affecting made afraid to get locked. If voices a little whistle. Put through pain internal as an injury cannot heal broken bone&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8276797.0.jpeg?02058986&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Jessop Avenue, Montpellier, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8276797&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8276797</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:31:59 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.901022 -2.084668</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flytipping on pavement - blocking access to pavement, 10th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8276760</link>
<description>Outside number 47 Zoons Road lots of waste on pavement which looks to be mostly large fencing panels which is blocking access to pavement. Unsure if this is the residents waste but either way it has been there for at least a month on the pavement.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8276760.0.jpeg?e4fbf52c&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Zoons Road, Hucclecote, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8276760&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping (not witnessed and no evidence likely)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8276760</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:17:18 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.85775 -2.184727</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fridge dumped, 9th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8276136</link>
<description>Fridge dumped&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 25, Willowleaze, Longlevens, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8276136&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping (not witnessed and no evidence likely)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8276136</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:20:39 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.871186 -2.208993</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>2 x Potholes, 9th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8276134</link>
<description>2 Potholes in the road&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 25, Willowleaze, Longlevens, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8276134&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8276134</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:19:50 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.871186 -2.208993</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Traffic lights on Westfield Rd, 9th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275807</link>
<description>Traffic lights on westfield road Brockworth only lets 4 cars to go where as Golf club lane lets 10 plus go&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Westfield Road, Brockworth, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275807&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Timings are incorrect</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275807</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:33:05 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.848675 -2.167279</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Damaged footpath, 9th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275697</link>
<description>Workmen have damaged the footpath again driving/parking on there slabs are broken&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8275697.0.jpeg?92472576&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 2, Pennine Road, Lynworth, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275697&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275697</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:05:11 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.906808 -2.049874</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Green light not working on the traffic signals, 9th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275651</link>
<description>Pedestrian crossing outside the exit from the Barracks.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Innsworth Lane, Innsworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275651&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Green or amber traffic light is not working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275651</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:56:41 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.889701 -2.19809</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The right hand filter light doesn’t come on, 9th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275556</link>
<description>The right hand lane filter light doesn’t come on so traffic coming from Elmbridge court roundabout direction wanting to turn right onto Old Cheltenham Road queue all the way back up to Nine Elms Road because people are relying on gaps in the traffic to turn right, causing unnecessary queues. This worked well before the new lights were installed&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 159, Cheltenham Road, Longlevens, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275556&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Green or amber traffic light is not working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275556</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:36:50 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.875109 -2.207583</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Poor road finish which will breakdown and cause issues., 9th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275076</link>
<description>This road has just been redone but they have not followed the map sent out showing the junction being tarmaced into dunster road further in. The new tarmac will not last with the traffic flow if this does not get carriee on a few meters into Dunster road, following origional plan sent to home owners. They are on site tomorrow friday 10th October please can you sort&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Regards&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8275076.0.jpeg?54d78c41&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 20, Dunster Road, Fiddler&#39;s Green, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275076&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Poor repairs (reinstatement)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275076</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:58:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.906658 -2.122843</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Verge of Churchtown Road from A417 Overbridge to hucclecote footpath 5 is obstructed by vegetation, 9th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275026</link>
<description>Verge of Churchtown Road from A417 Overbridge to hucclecote footpath 5 is obstructed by vegetation&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This is a safety hazard to pedestrians&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8275026.0.jpeg?dc015982&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Brockworth Road, Brockworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275026&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Causing obstruction to pavement/road (Grass/verge)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8275026</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:47:37 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.854909 -2.157236</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>