<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Unpermitted roadworks problem, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666847</link>
<description>Customer is calling and says a telegraph post has been installed on the footway next to their property. They say it is close to their boundary wall and is looming over their property. They are also concerned that if this may fall it would go onto their property. They have spoken to engineers and they have told them to raise an objection with GCC.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666847&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Unpermitted roadworks</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666847</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 14:25:02 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.849655 -2.160722</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large flytip, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666547</link>
<description>Gateway just after sliproad from M5 junction 8 joins the Tewkesbury Road Cheltenham there is a gate way with what looks like a lot of timber and building rubbish. I saw it while travelling towards Coombe hill.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Tewkesbury Road, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666547&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666547</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 14:21:15 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.927442 -2.135503</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree is damaged problem, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666566</link>
<description>FMS report fwd by CBC 03.06.25 - Dead tree to the rear of 15 Lypiatt Terrace in Lypiatt Lane. I understand that I am not allowed to remove this but need to report it to you for removal. Thank you.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666566&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666566</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:12:01 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.893314 -2.085896</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree is damaged problem, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666564</link>
<description>FMS report fwd by CBC 03.06.25 - Fallen Tree across byeway.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666564&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666564</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:05:28 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.922989 -2.102568</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overhanging trees and branches, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666250</link>
<description>The road through upper coberley is thwart with trees, bushes, roses from gardens and overgrown verges - it makes it very dangerous as you can’t see round corners especially on the houses.. cyclists whizz round corners and walkers with dogs.. it’s only a matter of time before there is an accident&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7666250.0.jpeg?86a006d9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Coberley, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666250&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree overhanging/overgrown limb</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666250</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:33:11 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.840073 -2.033775</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Storm drain blocked between Green Cottage and the drainage ditch opposite, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666247</link>
<description>The drainage ditch to the rear of the Old Meeting House feeds into an underground pipe (Point A) that runs under the rear of Yew Tree Lodge and on to an access chamber to the rear of Green Cottage (Point B). I have &amp;#39;rodded&amp;#39; this section and it appears to be clear. I have attempted to rod from point B towards point C but the pipe is blocked approximately 24 metres from Point B. I believe the pipe should exit into the drainage ditch at Point C.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;As a result of this blockage the drainage ditch to the rear of The Old Meeting House fills and eventually floods The Old Meeting House, Green Cottage and the rear of Elm Lodge. This last happened in September 2024.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I am aware that this issue has already been reported but I though it would be helpful to add some detail.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7666247.0.jpeg?cad6efb9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666247&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7666247</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:32:53 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.946835 -2.131521</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree is breaking and will fall across the road very soon, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665984</link>
<description>The tree issue is in Stanley Pontlarge, you turn into the village and head up the road, you drive under the railway bridge then there is a right hand bend and the tree is on that bend on the left hand side.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7665984.0.jpeg?dd8f8cf3&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Prescott, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665984&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665984</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.970924 -2.00169</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Verge not maintained for 2 years, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665809</link>
<description>The verge on New Street along the northern edge of the Waitrose site has not had any maintenance for the past 2 years. It is an eyesore, overgrown with brambles and passersby throw rubbish into it, including supermarket trolleys and traffic cones.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7665809.0.jpeg?79b3d2f0&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 77, New Street, St Paul’s, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665809&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Parks/landscapes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665809</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:18:01 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.902779 -2.08327</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The drain is blocked problem, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665718</link>
<description>Email received 04/06/2025 - copy attached. Customer reports that, during rainfall, water flows consistently from the road into the location, leading to flooding. They ask if Highways can investigate, suggesting that a later of tarmac could resolve the issue.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665718&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665718</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:45:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.886577 -2.138437</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Obstruction to visibility at the junction near High Groove Way, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665577</link>
<description>I am writing to raise concerns about the hedge at No. 1 Essex Close, GL31NZ, which has been planted illegally and is causing a serious obstruction to visibility at the junction near High Groove Way. This hedge has led to numerous near misses and is putting road users at unnecessary risk. After conducting thorough investigations, including reviewing property deeds and estate plans, it is clear that this hedge has been planted outside the property&amp;#39;s legal boundary for personal gain. The household at No. 1 Essex Close has no legal claim to estate land or council land, and this hedge must therefore be removed immediately. Drivers approaching this junction struggle to see oncoming traffic without having to dangerously edge their vehicles into the road. In addition, the presence of streetlights buried within the hedge clearly indicates that it extends beyond the property boundary and onto council land. The red fence behind the hedge further proves that the planting is outside the rightful boundary of the property. Under Section 154 of the Highways Act 1980, the council has the authority to require the removal or trimming of any vegetation obstructing visibility and causing a danger to road users. Part 8 of the Anti-social Behaviour Act 2003 also allows councils to take action where high hedges negatively impact public safety and enjoyment of a space. This is not just an inconvenience—it is a safety hazard that affects local residents and tax-paying motorists. The selfish actions of one household should not endanger others or make daily driving unnecessarily difficult. I urge the council to take swift and decisive action to remove this hedge and restore safe visibility at this junction. I look forward to your prompt response and to seeing the necessary steps taken as soon as possible.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7665577.0.jpeg?0b55dd74&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Highgrove Way, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665577&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocking visibility on road/junction (Grass/verge)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665577</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:42:46 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.892664 -2.189708</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Light sensor is not detecting vehicles problem, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665494</link>
<description>Police have been called regarding the lights on the junction of Charlton Lane, as there needs to be three way lights on this junction as no one is aware when they need to go. can this be looked into please.  &#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665494&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Light sensor is not detecting vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665494</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:18:17 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.879844 -2.070875</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trees are totally covering any sight of the traffic lights, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665057</link>
<description>On the A40 the trees need to be taken right back further down the A40 from the Petrol Station to the traffic lights as it is impossible to see the lights until you reach them. There are large yellow warning signs advising lights in 400yds but most people miss them completely. The trees need to be cut at the top, not just the bottom section.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): A40, Andoversford, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665057&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree causing damage/obstruction to pavement or road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7665057</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 09:29:48 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.867622 -1.961575</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Traffic lights completely obscured by trees, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7664652</link>
<description>The traffic lights on the A40 where it meets the A436 at Shipton Olliffe. Specifically the lights on the A40 as you approach from cheltenham The lights cannot be seen until you are within a few meters of the junction&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): A40, Shipton, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7664652&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7664652</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 08:01:13 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.864048 -1.958434</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Loads of large potholes around the whole of Clevedon square about 10in total all larger than a dinner plate and deep enough that motorbikes could be dismounted, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7664448</link>
<description>All of the Clevedon square loop GL518BJ&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1-6, Clevedon Square, Rowanfield, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7664448&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7664448</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 06:20:07 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.903621 -2.100986</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Unexpected loud works started at 5:20am, 5th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7664424</link>
<description>A manhole cover outside 18 and 20 Robert Burns avenue.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7664424.0.jpeg?e6403093&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 30, Robert Burns Avenue, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7664424&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Unpermitted roadworks</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7664424</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:43:46 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.891148 -2.118162</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>20 inch pothole in layby on A435, 4th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7663767</link>
<description>The pothole is on the left hand side of the layby that sits southbound just past the junction with the B4079. It is a short way from the entrance to the layby. I do not know how long it has been there.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7663767.0.jpeg?74a5190d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): A435, Oxenton, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7663767&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Car parking</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7663767</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 20:50:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.983027 -2.071755</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Vegetation obstructing complete view of chicane., 4th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7663700</link>
<description>The traffic calming chicane on Gotherington lane. Whilst the vegetation has been cleared from one entry into the chicane, visibility from the other end is obscured by long grass and presents a risk to all road traffic. The vegetation is a very obvious risk from all points in this chicane and it needs to be regularly cleared before an accident occurs.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Gotherington Lane, Gotherington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7663700&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocking visibility on road/junction (Grass/verge)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7663700</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 20:32:30 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.955884 -2.053985</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Private property, 4th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7663533</link>
<description>The alleyway between 349 innsworth lane and Boleyn close&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 4, Boleyn Close, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7663533&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Causing obstruction to pavement/road (Grass/verge)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7663533</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:49:27 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.88934 -2.190522</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trench filling is moving under load, 4th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7662893</link>
<description>There are 2 trenches in this road that have been filled. However heavey lorries are making the filling move leaving deep potholes. The trench needs digging out and the correct grade tarmac refilling.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): A435, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7662893&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Poor repairs (reinstatement)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7662893</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 17:30:57 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.936375 -2.065465</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Traffic calming on Gotherington lane is dangerous, 4th June</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7662868</link>
<description>The Traffic calming on Gotherington lane is dangerous as the verges are not maintained on a monthly basis. It is not easy to see oncoming traffic....particularly if the vehicle is not tall. Seeing cyclists is also an issue. Please remove the traffic calming ASAP. It would be far safer to have just a speed camera. Thereby limiting speed, maintaining traffic flow and causing less pollution due to unecessary stop start.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Gotherington Lane, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7662868&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7662868</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 17:25:59 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.954469 -2.054865</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>