<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Overflowing bin, 28th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940687</link>
<description>Clearly been missed on collection run&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7940687.0.jpeg?b3be1f81&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 64, Finchcroft Lane, Noverton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940687&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Rubbish (refuse and recycling)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940687</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 06:17:14 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.909138 -2.038963</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>&#39;Pedestrian &#39; white markkng logo needed, 28th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940660</link>
<description>A40 road crossing in Cheltenham. Pedestrians are using cycle lane, which is marked, to cross the road. See photos. Pedestrian &amp;#39; white markkng logo needed please to avoid the risk of collisions.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7940660.0.jpeg?266b0735&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): A40, Montpellier, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940660&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road markings, lines and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940660</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:48:22 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.894545 -2.083219</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abbey Terrace Dangerous Surface for mobility user, 28th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940642</link>
<description>Resident Reported The pavement along Abbey Terrace needs some TLC, particularly the entrance to The Abbey where it crosses the pavement. I am a mobility scooter user and find the uneven surface difficult to navigate. The problem with the surface arose a year or so ago when substantial works were carried out at The Abbey and the many heavy lorries used in the building work created two distinct ruts across the pavement. I had expected that some remedial work would be carried out in due course but this does not appear to be the case. Using the pavement yesterday evening caused my scooter to lean at a frightening angle and at one point I really thought that it would tip over.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Can you please ask the powers that be to inspect the area and carry out some repair work.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Abbey Terrace, Winchcombe, Winchcombe&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940642&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940642</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:02:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.952737 -1.965364</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Someone tresspassed into stole my garden and stole my clean bin claarly marked 28a Oakleaze and left theiir dirty bin in my garden, 28th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940617</link>
<description>Myself and mt wife were away for the weekend. Someone sneaked into my garden and left their dirty disgusting bin. They took my clean bin which clearly has a sticker for 28a Oakleaze. They filled it to the brim with their dirty child&amp;#39;s disgusting nappies and rotten milk, and tried to cover it. I feel distressed and violated. Understand they might have difficulties, but that is not my issue. Absolutely disgusting and theft.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7940617.0.jpeg?7b9581d0&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 39, Oakleaze, Elmbridge, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940617&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Large-scale illegal dumping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940617</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 02:24:22 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.872941 -2.208346</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>ADE 60 Bridge missing and route impassable, 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940350</link>
<description>ADE60 at SO 87919 27610 passes over a wide drainage channel. It is totally overgrown and impassable, but there is no bridge so it would be impassable even if the vegetation was cleared. However, there is a way around by going through a gate at Grid Ref: SO 87784 27593 which does have a way mark on the gatepost. Assuming that there no cash in the GCC coffers for a new bridge the current informal route should be designated as the PROW by a DMMO.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7940350.0.jpeg?c045643d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Pancake Lane, Leigh, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940350&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Bridge is damaged/missing</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940350</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:50:49 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.946892 -2.177131</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>In front of our property there are two trees situated very close to each other . Unfortunately the trees are being used by local children as goalpost while playing football and frequently hitting our fence and main door, 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940289</link>
<description>Infront of 6 Goldsmith Road, Churchdown, GL31FX&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7940289.0.jpeg?23b91fb9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Webster Road, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940289&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940289</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:32:25 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.882984 -2.197065</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Column 13 High street permanently on, 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940127</link>
<description>One lamp on post constantly on during daytime&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7940127.0.jpeg?48891ebc&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 356, High Street, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940127&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940127</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 20:37:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.903965 -2.081323</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pothole / Surface Damage, 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940014</link>
<description>On roundabout just off Cheltenham Rd junction.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cheltenham Road, Elmbridge, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940014&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pothole (NH)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7940014</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 20:08:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.878629 -2.201128</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Extremely long grass and weeds blocking vision and looking extremely untidy., 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7939845</link>
<description>Whole length of Finlay Way, traffic islands on and verges on either side of Bishops Cleeve By-pass. Dangerous for motorists given that high grass blocks visibility and to pedestrians - especially small children. Helping to create health issues for those of us who suffer from allergies to grass and weed pollen. It is also an utter disgrace that our village now looks so uncared for and scruffy when Cleeve must be one of the biggest contributors to Council Tax across the county. Disgusting. We need the verges cut regularly as in nearby Cheltenham which looks beautiful in comparison.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Finlay Way, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7939845&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocking visibility on road/junction (Grass/verge)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7939845</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 18:58:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.948912 -2.065454</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>5ft pothole near drive way entrance, 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7939786</link>
<description>22 Greatfield Drive Charlton Kings GL539BY&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7939786.0.jpeg?848aaf38&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 10, Greatfield Drive, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7939786&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7939786</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 18:40:50 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.879293 -2.065834</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Griffiti on road at 4 locations on Bushcombe Lane, 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7939317</link>
<description>Graffiti on the road at 4 locations going up from Single Pippin on Bushcombe Lane, Woodmancote. Three include snails, the 4th is a smiley face. What3words: - dollars.flinches.agents - teardrop.objecting.cube - wisely.drives.chuckling - cross.noticing.germinate&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7939317.0.jpeg?3864b974&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bushcombe Lane, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7939317&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7939317</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 16:15:49 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.949694 -2.032916</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree causing damage to wall, 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7939117</link>
<description>The tree outside 142 Brooklyn road Cheltenham.Has caused our front brick wall to split overnight, and is also pushing up the pavement .The wall is double bricked with 28 inches x 18 inches deep footings .The tree has also got lots of dead branches on it which are also a concern .&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 141, Brooklyn Road, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7939117&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree causing damage to property</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7939117</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 15:17:10 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.905758 -2.106819</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>2 temporary excavation covers - 5yrs here now, 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938881</link>
<description>There are two plastic covers on excavations which have been like this for over 5 years - I have email trail to prove this. They’re slowly starting to disintegrate due to age. Please can the holes be filled in and the verge restored?&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7938881.0.jpeg?4f01d490&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Up Hatherley Way, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938881&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs &amp; Barriers left behind by Contractor</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938881</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:22:08 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.879069 -2.107456</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Footpaths ASH 8 &amp; ASH 9 impassable, 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938720</link>
<description>Junction of footpaths and for some distance leading to that junction. I tried to use the PROW from Hatherley Cricket Club to pick up the footpath which should run from Leckhampton Lane to Shurdington Rd this morning. When I came near to the &amp;#39;T&amp;#39; junction of these paths it was impossible to find a way through. I retraced my steps to the Cricket club and came along the A46 to try and find the path from the Shurdington Rd end. Again I was thwarted by vegetation. This is the second time this year I have reported the state of these paths and I see that at least one other person has reported it. This path is an important route for people wishing to avoid the busy A46 and it is a legal right of way. I would appreciate an early site visit from your representatives and proper reinstatement of these footpaths. Thank you.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Leckhampton Lane, Shurdington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938720&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Obstruction caused by tree</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938720</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:30:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.869077 -2.107391</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overgrown, abandoned public grass space, 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938571</link>
<description>The large grass area area in the middle of Beverley Gardens has been abandoned since Tewkesbury Borough Council handed back grass cutting to GCC Highways in 2024. The area is overgrown, in places over 1m high. Visibility on these bends is already a problem due to high hedges and parked cars. Seeing oncoming traffic as you move onto off off your drive is increasingly hazardous due to the current neglect. The grass cannot be allowed to grown unchecked for ever - which appears to be TBC and GCC&amp;#39;s intent. Residents plan to attack the area with scythes - have we really come to this?&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7938571.0.jpeg?d62b3ee2&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Beverley Gardens, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938571&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocking visibility on road/junction (Grass/verge)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938571</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 12:53:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.944852 -2.040133</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The large public grass area at Byfield Close has not been cut since Tewkesbury Borough Council handed grass cutting responsibility back to Gloucestershire County Council Highways in 2024. The area is overgrown, apparently abandoned by both TBC and GCC and in urgent need of cutting., 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938550</link>
<description>Byfield Close - you can&amp;#39;t miss the jungle if you visit. It is between 2,3,5,8 and 11 Byfield Close.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7938550.0.jpeg?f6e5c338&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Byfield Close, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938550&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Blocking visibility on road/junction (Grass/verge)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938550</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 12:45:34 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.941267 -2.043344</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Road sweeping required, 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938327</link>
<description>Road sweeping required along the lenght of market street&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7938327.0.jpeg?4b3657f4&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 8, Market Street, St Paul’s, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938327&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938327</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:46:26 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.903298 -2.084809</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Poor pavement surface, 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938210</link>
<description>The footway in Monson Avenue is very poor and needs re-surfacing.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 10, Monson Avenue, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938210&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938210</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:13:03 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.904692 -2.074802</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sunken drain grate., 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938145</link>
<description>Garage side just after centre island.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): A435, Gotherington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938145&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938145</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 10:59:47 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.964423 -2.069667</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>No through road sign required.Monks Lane., 27th July</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938117</link>
<description>Monks Lane is a single track road, and is being used by trafic looking for a short cut including lorries,It is a dead end so vehicles have to turn and go back which is difficult for some large vehicles.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Monks Lane, Ashchurch Rural, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938117&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign plate is missing (Non illuminating sign)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7938117</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 10:52:41 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.979708 -2.114599</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>