<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Access and route overgrown, 31st May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7641376</link>
<description>Access to the stile is totally blocked by hedge and overgrown foliage. The footpath is also unmaintained and if you could access, you can’t walk because you can’t get through.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7641376.0.jpeg?7d29c027&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Frog Furlong Lane, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7641376&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Crops are blocking/growing on route</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7641376</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 07:42:03 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.897061 -2.204589</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gate obstructed and no signage, 31st May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7641372</link>
<description>Unable to access gate as hedgerow is blocking. No obvious signage.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7641372.0.jpeg?6e1e304a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Frog Furlong Lane, Down Hatherley, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7641372&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Gate is damaged/missing/locked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7641372</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 07:39:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.899242 -2.205212</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>No signage, 31st May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7641362</link>
<description>Overgrown and no signage to direct which way to walk. No obvious foot path and crop in entire field.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7641362.0.jpeg?7eddfa51&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Frog Furlong Lane, Down Hatherley, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7641362&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Crops are blocking/growing on route</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7641362</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 07:38:17 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.901555 -2.205523</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subsided tarmac around water stop tap (recent STW job, now about 50mm deep), 30th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7640087</link>
<description>On footpath outside 75 Alma Road,&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 75, Alma Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7640087&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7640087</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 17:26:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.885685 -2.11052</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trees on corner of Longway Avenue/parkwood Grove too big and damaging footpath, 30th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7640035</link>
<description>2 trees, maple I believe, on the corner of Longway Avenue to Parkwood Grove are very large and tall and are beginning to damage the public footpath. They are also continuing to block the sunlight to our garden and growing over our garden. Please can someone inspect the trees and cut them down and back.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 7, Longway Avenue, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7640035&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7640035</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 17:16:00 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.877108 -2.057926</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree overhanging private gardens and blocking access to public footpath, 30th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7639950</link>
<description>I am writing to formally bring to your attention an issue concerning a tree located on the verge outside 211 &amp;amp; 213 Hewlett road Cheltenham. The tree in question is overhanging private gardens but extends significantly into the public footpath, causing a serious obstruction for pedestrians. This overgrowth not only impedes safe passage but also poses a potential hazard, especially for individuals with mobility difficulties, parents with strollers, and cyclists. The tree in question is owned and maintained by the council. Its overhanging branches are encroaching into our private gardens and obstructing the public footpath, creating a hazard for pedestrians and impeding access. According to local regulations and the council&amp;#39;s responsibilities under the Highways Act 1980 (or relevant local legislation), the council has a duty to maintain trees on public land to prevent such obstructions. I kindly request that the council take immediate action to trim the overhanging branches and ensure the safety and accessibility of the footpath and gardens. Kind regards Caroline Armer Fisher&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 205, Hewlett Road, Battledown, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7639950&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7639950</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 16:50:11 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.901136 -2.056813</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>SUGGESTION : Could you add a &#39;50mph&#39; repeater sign near the airfield ?, 30th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7639675</link>
<description>SUGGESTION : Could you add a &amp;#39;50mph&amp;#39; repeater sign near the airfield please ? You were kind enough to add a 50 repeater on the north bound staverton lane recently (north of the traffic lights), but there is no corresponding repeater sign on the southbound side, until you get to or just past the M5 bridge. Would it be possible to add one in where feasible and appropriate please ? Thanks again for the other extra sign on the north of the traffic lights !&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Bamfurlong Lane, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7639675&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign plate is missing (Non illuminating sign)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7639675</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 16:04:56 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.897617 -2.159161</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fallen tree close to Road has blocked customers water outflow from sceptic tank., 30th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7639334</link>
<description>Tree is by my house GL54 5AG called Dryfield Meadow Barn. Think it was struck by lightning or bad storm as it’s split in half. Looks very dangerous and other half could fall. Have checked boundary and it is on highway side.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7639334.0.jpeg?a3d6674e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cheltenham Road, Winchcombe, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7639334&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree causing damage/obstruction to pavement or road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7639334</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 15:09:22 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.948556 -2.001486</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fly tipping, 30th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7639151</link>
<description>Guess what?? More rubbish has been dumped here last night. The sofa and chair that were there for a week have now gone. But within 24 hours more rubbish arrives. Happens nearly every week and has done for years. Why do you do nothing to prevent it happening or to fine the people responsible?? It makes a fairly tatty part of town look like a rubbish dump.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 66, Pates Avenue, Alstone, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7639151&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7639151</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:34:12 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.902082 -2.093603</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Double yellow lines at the junction of Charlton Park Drive and Old Bath Rd. GL53 7, 30th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7638947</link>
<description>These lines. are faded + obscured with dirt. They need re painting as cars are regularly parked over them reducing the width of the road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Charlton Park Drive, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7638947&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road markings, lines and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7638947</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:01:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.887673 -2.068003</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post or sign leaning slightly (less than 20 degrees) problem, 30th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7637511</link>
<description>Antisemitic political propaganda stickers&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7637511&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Post or sign leaning slightly (less than 20 degrees)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7637511</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:42:50 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.892793 -2.089766</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Junction of Clarade Street and St Georges Place, 30th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7637011</link>
<description>The junction here was recently relined, but the condition of the road surface wasn&amp;#39;t addressed. The uneven surface is a danger to all road users especially cyclists. Indeed the condition of the road surface along many stretches of Clarence Street is wholly inadequate and extremely undulating for all vehicle users. More needs to be done and if only each relevant department could communicate with one other it may help improve the condition of our roads and safety of those who use it. STOP WASTING MINE AND OTHERS COUNCIL TAX MONEY PLEASE 🙏&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7637011.0.jpeg?5d1b7d00&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 61;61a, Clarence Street, St Paul’s, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7637011&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7637011</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:42:05 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.901408 -2.078648</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Stop line faded so cars go over cycle protective advanced box., 30th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7636833</link>
<description>Locatiom : Junction of The Park with Ashford Road travelling towards Cheltenham town centre. White lines need repainting to make drivers aware they are going over designated box area.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7636833.0.jpeg?5a8fda68&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 29, Park Place, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7636833&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road markings, lines and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7636833</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:56:39 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.890174 -2.084701</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree growth obscuring view of bus coming, 30th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7636585</link>
<description>The tree to the side of the bus stop is sprouting so much that you can’t see whether your bus is coming&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lansdown Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7636585&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7636585</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:25:44 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.894194 -2.097017</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overgrown tree - sticky sap, debris and scratches car, 30th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7636413</link>
<description>Tree that has significantly overgrown above designated parking space number 34 on Brockweir Rd, Cheltenham GL52 5FP.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Large tree regularly drops sticky sap and debris onto vehicles, which not only obscures the windows by creating a solid sticky residue - creating a potential safety hazard, a slippery surface around vehicles when wet - but also damages the paintwork.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In addition to the sap, overhanging branches have begun scratching car doors, to the extent that it is now required to park partially on the road to try to avoid further damage.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7636413.0.jpeg?f225c1d7&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 32;36;38;40;42;44;46;48, Brockweir Road, Oakley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7636413&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7636413</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:39:14 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.901598 -2.042369</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rough road surface, 30th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7635635</link>
<description>This is a very rough road with deep troughs in the middle. It has been like this for years&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Mary Rose Avenue, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7635635&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7635635</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:10:45 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.890481 -2.191114</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface problem, 29th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7634157</link>
<description>Customer reports that the pavement at the location is cracked and broken up and the water meter cover has sunk - it&amp;#39;s a trip hazard. STW were due to replace/repair/change the meter, but the sub-contractor on site yesterday advised that, whilst they had attended to other meters locally, they had no Streetworks permit to repair this one. Their overriding concern is the condition of the pavement and the potential safety hazard to pedestrians. They ask if Highways can investigate, as this affects the pavement.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7634157&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Other damage to pavement i.e. cobbles, raised mound/surface</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7634157</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:38:06 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.883795 -2.080488</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Developers Sign Blocking View, 29th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7634009</link>
<description>There is a developers sign blocking the view of teh A435 whilst you&amp;#39;re waiting to turn out from Malleson Road. This is at a black spot for accidents. Please remove / place somewhere else.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Malleson Road, Gotherington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7634009&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign plate is misaligned</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7634009</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:36:48 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.965153 -2.069731</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>New flytipping, 29th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7633907</link>
<description>New flytipping in usual lay-by on bypass between Zoons Court roundabout &amp;amp; Glos Business Park.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/7633907.0.jpeg?33c5d425&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hucclecote, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7633907&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7633907</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:20:48 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.854838 -2.175383</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Someone requested the reopening of this lay-by and they seem to have had their request approved, without any consultation or thought given to how this would affect the local residents living directly opposite this lay-by. Why was this ? And the residents would like to request that the lay-by be closed permanently., 29th May</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7633765</link>
<description>Lay-by on A417 between Elmbridge Court roundabout and the c&amp;amp;G roundabout.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): A417, Elmbridge, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7633765&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road markings, lines and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/7633765</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:27:56 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.875404 -2.199272</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>