<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Yellow lines stop too close to pedestrian island meaning cars and emergency services cannot pass without going the other side of the road, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252975</link>
<description>The start of Barley road as you turn off New Barn Land&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Barley Road, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252975&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road markings, lines and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252975</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 19:32:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913969 -2.057597</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apparently abandoned vehicle, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252860</link>
<description>That is a vehicle. Apparently abandoned at the far end of Old Reddings Road, Cheltenham, where it becomes the path alongside the park (sometimes known as the &amp;quot;Humpty dumps&amp;quot;). Reg OY58 BFJ, dark Volvo estate. It has been there about a week so I wondered if abandoned or stolen and dumped.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8252860.0.jpeg?caa9d890&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Old Reddings Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252860&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252860</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 18:31:28 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.887577 -2.12606</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Door 39, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252697</link>
<description>Look at the state they leave in front of the fence. Who’s fault if break down the fence? So who street link, the Council, Road Worker. Working for? Just fixing the street without no incomes, go to the supermarket without no money, where does the refuse truck gets paid. If carry the rubbish to dump. Take receipt who pay? Now who take the risk an allowed government boundary not be clear. None as Landlord resident reported if it is Street Sweeper meant to sweep outside their gate&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please this is an serious matter i wrote my full life story call the emergency felt sorry from 2020. Now wants me to Starve not giving no jobs. Testing if attempted suffer cold Starving they find spite have the purpose to start stealing. No family not giving my compensation in construction but after benefit Claim in my names again use the same method if put under mental health use entitle eligible to find accommodation an put you on benefit. Why they do not help with jobs an find accommodation? Why not building work environment instead of businesses supermarket restaurant activity. Why not have accommodation cheat as shelter prison room.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Why after Mental health to give free Benefit Claim. Look in all the homeless Centre if only allowed strangers in they premises giving away free food an putting them on benefit using needs to find accommodation an make government pay for they housing benefit&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8252697.0.jpeg?2a4654a9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 32, Market Street, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252697&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252697</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.904088 -2.085785</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ditch with cables not filled in many months ago, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252513</link>
<description>Green Lane, Little Witcombe, near retirement mobile homes.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8252513.0.jpeg?d950503b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Green Lane, Badgeworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252513&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned materials</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252513</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 18:03:46 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.837349 -2.129029</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cycle path closed/cyclists dismount here signs - but cycle lane clearly open, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252485</link>
<description>Signs placed closing the cycle lane and advising cyclists to dismount. I chose to use the road as requested and was subject to abuse by motorists along this section. Could the signs be removed or swapped for ‘cyclists rejoin carriageway’ if the cycle lane is clear please.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8252485.0.jpeg?938e8ba8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cheltenham Road East, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252485&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs &amp; Barriers left behind by Contractor</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252485</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:52:41 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.897004 -2.174411</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree branch broken and hanging over Beeches playground, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252373</link>
<description>A large branch has snapped and remained stuck in the tree. It&amp;#39;s in the playground at the Beeches in Charlton Kings. It&amp;#39;s overhanging and could fall into the playground.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8252373.0.jpeg?1448cfa9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Sappercombe Lane, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252373&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252373</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:19:18 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.880044 -2.049243</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Request for Extension of Yellow Line Markings to Improve Safety and Emergency Access, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252336</link>
<description>Top of barley road, the first island, near new barn lane. This has been an ongoing issue since the yellow lines were painted on earlier this year.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I am writing to raise a safety concern regarding the current layout of road markings near [insert specific location or junction name]. The existing yellow lines terminate too early before the traffic island, which results in vehicles being forced to bypass the island on the wrong side of the road. This creates a significant hazard and obstructs the passage of emergency vehicles, which would otherwise have to mount or cross the island to proceed — posing risks to both the vehicle and road users. According to the Traffic Signs Regulations and General Directions (TSRGD) 2016, yellow line restrictions (no waiting or no loading) must be positioned so that they clearly convey the extent of the restriction and maintain safe, unobstructed access for traffic. In this instance, the current termination point does not adequately prevent obstruction nor ensure a clear passage for emergency response vehicles, as required under Section 130 of the Highways Act 1980, which places a duty on highway authorities to assert and protect the rights of the public to the use and enjoyment of the highway. I respectfully request that the double yellow lines be extended beyond the island to ensure: Vehicles can remain fully on the correct side of the carriageway; Emergency vehicles can pass safely without mounting kerbs or traffic islands; and Compliance with visibility and obstruction standards as set out in the Design Manual for Roads and Bridges (DMRB), CD 169 – Traffic Signs and Road Markings. I would appreciate an inspection of the site and a confirmation that this matter will be reviewed under the authority’s road safety and maintenance obligations. Thank you for your attention to this issue again. I look forward to your response.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8252336.0.jpeg?7356696b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Barley Road, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252336&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Line issue (Parking)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252336</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:10:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913969 -2.057597</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Park gate needs adjustment, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252299</link>
<description>The gate here doesn&amp;#39;t close. A little planing on the outer edge or adjusting the catch will sort it.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8252299.0.jpeg?1e0d0b86&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Station Road, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252299&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Parks/landscapes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252299</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:01:57 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.884105 -2.167585</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Drain blocked, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252255</link>
<description>Outside number 66&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 62, Malleson Road, Gotherington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252255&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252255</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:50:26 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.965407 -2.058361</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lowered pavement not lowered enough for wheelchair use and my son was tipped out of her wheelchair causing pain to injured toes, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8251970</link>
<description>On the corner of Regent street and county court road&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8251970.0.jpeg?f489d714&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 16, Regent Street, Montpellier, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8251970&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The kerb is damaged/missing</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8251970</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 14:24:42 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.897986 -2.076569</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Large tree branch damaged by the wind and hanging down., 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8251963</link>
<description>Outside numbers 10 &amp;amp; 12 Monica Drive, Pittville, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 24, Monica Drive, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8251963&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8251963</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 14:22:03 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.912576 -2.073243</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Volunteer litter pick bags ready for collection (4th October), 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8251940</link>
<description>Innsworth Lane Sports Ground. The &amp;#39;What 3 Words&amp;#39; location is ///examiner.slopes.courage The ordnance survey map reference is: 51.883919,-2.213313 Council Litter Bin Ref: 0254&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8251940.0.jpeg?ec9cf5f4&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Innsworth Lane, Longlevens, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8251940&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Litter picking bags ready for collection</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8251940</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 14:15:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.883874 -2.213312</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubbish tipped in Winston Churchill Memorial Gardens, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8251585</link>
<description>Rubbish tipped in Winston Churchill Memorial Gardens&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8251585.0.jpeg?0957580b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Honeybourne, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8251585&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8251585</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 12:42:58 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.904582 -2.084767</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Two large hessian rugs, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250741</link>
<description>Two large hessian rugs on Eastern Avenue at turning for Smyths Toys.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8250741.0.jpeg?8622f448&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hucclecote Road, Hucclecote, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250741&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250741</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 09:07:27 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.85064 -2.173216</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Full litter bin, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250734</link>
<description>Yet again this main bin was not changed on Thursday&amp;#39;s routine bin change. It is the most used yet continually gets missed. I&amp;#39;ve since added a red litter bag for collection. Top of Hucclecote Road at us stop &amp;amp; junction of lights with Glos Biz Park.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8250734.0.jpeg?902fc15e&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hucclecote Road, Hucclecote, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250734&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Rubbish (refuse and recycling)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250734</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 09:04:45 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.85064 -2.173216</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pointed trees Park Street just as turned in on your left, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250628</link>
<description>I have report this same trees around Richmond Sainsbury&amp;#39;s in 2023. Nothing change about the safety of the environment. None care all the areas countrie in the UK is working in the same order. You understand kids playing out if only doing your jobs. Not report to the police are vote to the house of parliament. Cannot allowed underage out in public without someone over 18 as family members. Not working for the Emergency Service secured on open fields bush playground. What time you finished work but blame the Emergency to open 24/7 how many jobs your service wants to keep them? Please secure the bushes look for all trespass hiding putting up tents out of sight. Understand why they living that way. We wants all the big trees cut down an make equal boundary on half an half take ideas on the pavement inside the road over the next pavement look In between the line markers. that is how all the fences meant to be separate nothing hanging&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8250628.0.jpeg?453182f6&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 8, Park Street, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250628&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250628</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 08:27:36 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.90322 -2.084415</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Door 57, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250598</link>
<description>Please this is serious got to confronted the resident or the landlord. Look at that before any accident i send out the warning to be aware. How would this matter be resolved if resident blaming the Council got to call report. Some signs of threats the Council with Indian pakistan showing to increase bills rent using faults. They blame Government no confession in the emergency service.Cannot call police so Indian pakistan take advantage. Take over phone contract dealership finance. An use Rishi Sunak as they Prime Minister gets them in government businesses&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please sort out this matter urgent eyes do not sell at shop&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8250598.0.jpeg?453182f6&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 59, Market Street, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250598&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250598</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 08:13:51 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.904568 -2.08627</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The tree outside our house has still not been rectified. It still has a lot of dead branches which could very easily break and cause considerable damage in strong winds, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250500</link>
<description>Outside 29 and 31 Eldon Road&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8250500.0.jpeg?424aed8d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 29, Eldon Road, Ewens Farm, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250500&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250500</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 07:07:30 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.900094 -2.060124</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Three potholes near the riding school area, 3rd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250112</link>
<description>Residents are asking if we are going to fix the 3 large potholes on New Road whilst Severn Trent close the road to repair the burst water main. 3rd to 8th October. The three pots were reported on FixMyStreet last month there is a lot of local concern. You can&amp;#39;t miss them as they are getting bigger every day.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8250112.0.jpeg?73acc862&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): New Road, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250112&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8250112</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 21:11:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.936442 -2.043349</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cars skidding when manoeuvring, and noticeable bump when driving onto/off road, 3rd October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8249926</link>
<description>Outside number 43&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8249926.0.jpeg?d20369f9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Pinemount Road, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8249926&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8249926</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:05:58 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.85406 -2.186723</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>