<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>The alley way is absolutely full of fallen leaves and is incredibly slippy with so many extra pedestrians having to use it. It is also uneven in places making it difficult to navigate., 14th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8417103</link>
<description>The entire alley needs to be swept, between London Road and Hartlebury Way (Glenfall Way)&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 4, Courtfield Drive, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8417103&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8417103</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 07:49:41 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.885036 -2.046338</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>There is no street lighting, 14th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8417022</link>
<description>There is no street lighting at the end of the alleyway from Laxton Road to Green Lane making it pitch black, impossible to walk through the gate safely particularly with wet leaves making it slippy under foot.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8417022&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8417022</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 07:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.847338 -2.18739</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Drain blocked, brimmed with water and debris., 14th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416858</link>
<description>Outside 17 Ermin street.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8416858.0.jpeg?bd117ec9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 17, Ermin Street, Brockworth, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416858&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416858</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.847928 -2.165235</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Drain blocked, brimmed with water and debris., 14th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416855</link>
<description>Drone blocked in front of 19 Ermin street.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8416855.0.jpeg?4a55c53c&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 19, Ermin Street, Brockworth, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416855&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416855</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.847871 -2.165063</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The lane control approach sign is getting obscured again, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416810</link>
<description>The lane control approach sign from Churchdown towards Elmbridge Court Roundabout (A40 / A417) is getting obscured again by vegetation. Southbound, from Churchdown. Could the greenery be trimmed back again please ? TIA ! [NOTE : I&amp;#39;ve recently raised this via this app under &amp;#39;vegetation&amp;#39;, but I think it went to Glos City Council / Ubico, who said it was not their jurisdiction, and closed the request]&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cheltenham Road East, Elmbridge, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416810&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign plate is missing (Non illuminating sign)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416810</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.879765 -2.199859</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dangerous deep pothole, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416728</link>
<description>On the side with the pub but further towards gchq end of the road. I was cycling and had to swerve to avoid it, could easily have come off my bike.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 5, Whittington Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416728&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416728</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.894032 -2.119237</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ridiculous road closure that has no purpose, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416604</link>
<description>Please remove the road closed - residents access only signs that appear in our road every time there are races at the racecourse. They were put in place on Tuesday for races that I assume start tomorrow.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It serves no purpose - those who want free parking simply ignore it and come into the street and the traffic wardens cannot ticket them for doing so.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;We have several delivery drivers who haven’t delivered claiming they couldn’t access the street as it was unsafe to do so. This has cost us money as we had tradesmen waiting for urgent next day deliveries that didn’t come.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I’ve asked repeatedly last year and this “what is the purpose of these signs” and received no response.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please come asap and remove them - they are nonsensical, ugly and have no purpose whatsoever. They are now causing delivery issues too.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 6, Kensington Avenue, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416604&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Line issue (Parking)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416604</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.896255 -2.099381</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Road gulley along east side of old bath road full of leaf and other washed down litter stopping drains from operating, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416528</link>
<description>All rains from no 8 to 28 old bath road are effected&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 24, Old Bath Road, Fairview, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416528&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416528</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.891903 -2.066519</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Drain in road is blocked and not allowing any water to pass through, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416521</link>
<description>Norther of two drains with growing puddle around.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Recurring problem exacerbated by leaf and litter in gulleys which hasn&amp;#39;t been cleared&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 33, Old Bath Road, Fairview, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416521&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416521</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.892338 -2.066231</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Deep dangerous pothole, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416493</link>
<description>Yet another deep, large pothole on Whittington Road that could cause injury to a cyclist, particularly in dark wet conditions.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8416493.0.jpeg?d0e6f569&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 12, Whittington Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416493&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416493</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.894327 -2.120841</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>I deep and sharp and wide divot across the whole length of the road, also one further up towards the corner round onto chosen way, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416448</link>
<description>On colwell avenue just after the Wilkes avenue right hand turning, needs filling in and it’s a brutal divot and one exactly the same further up, makes a proper thud in the car and is unavoidable&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8416448.0.jpeg?c629e1dc&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Colwell Avenue, Hucclecote, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416448&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416448</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 20:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.860127 -2.186819</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Horrific road surface coming off churchdown lane into hucclecote, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416424</link>
<description>Coming off down the hill under the bridge into hucclecote on churchdown lane, before the speed bump before hucclecote rugby club turning. I know it’s been recently re surfaced in the past year but it’s absolutely abysmal and needs to be smooth, it’s ridiculously deep and bumpy, people still going on the other side of the road to avoid&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Churchdown Lane, Hucclecote, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416424&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416424</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 20:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.85768 -2.180138</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lasne Crescent sign vandalized in Brockworth, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416275</link>
<description>Lasne Crescent road sign vandalized, smashed down in June 2025? Road sink hole outside number 14 increased in depth?&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Lasne Crescent, Brockworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416275&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign has been vandalised (Non illuminating sign)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416275</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.842039 -2.15063</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Overgrown tree, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416179</link>
<description>Overgrown tree now growing into over-head telephone and fibre broadband cabling. See from pictures when full of leaves.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8416179.0.jpeg?cc961d70&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 29, The Grove, Ewens Farm, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416179&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Tree overhanging/overgrown limb</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416179</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.898191 -2.055381</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Streetlight not working, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416140</link>
<description>Streetlight outside 24 Litchfield Drive is not working&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 24, Lichfield Drive, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416140&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416140</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 18:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.881356 -2.097971</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Traffic light at junction of Winchcombe Street and Fairview road is faulty, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416094</link>
<description>The traffic light at the junction of Winchcombe Street and Fairview Road does not detect solo motorcycles and remains on red until a larger vehicle comes along to trigger it. When there is no traffic you have no choice other than to treat it as an uncontrolled junction, which is still technically an offence. This issue has been reported previously.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 15, Fairview Road, Ewens Farm, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416094&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Green or amber traffic light is not working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8416094</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 18:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.902172 -2.07123</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abandoned roadworks sign, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8415832</link>
<description>Christ Church Road, outside Christchurch Court (GL50 2PZ).&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Sign has been kicking around for months - was originally tied to a large cone on the road verge. Cone disappeared weeks ago but sign still on pavement.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Left behind by third party contractor, possibly. It&amp;#39;s now street junk and needs to be removed as whoever left it behind isn&amp;#39;t coming back for it.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Christchurch Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8415832&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs &amp; Barriers left behind by Contractor</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8415832</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 17:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.894333 -2.095377</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Diverted traffic signs, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8415806</link>
<description>Multiple &amp;quot;diverted traffic&amp;quot; signs - not clear what road closure / diversion they relate to?&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Queens Road - adjacent to traffic lights at Christ Church Road crossroads. A40 Lansdown Road - adjacent to traffic lights at Christ Church Road / Talbot Road crossroads. A40 Lansdown Road - outside Dean Close school A40 Westal Green (Texaco) roundabout - multiple.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;If for a current (live) diversion then fair enough, but if they were for a past diversion route which is no longer active then why are the signs still here (all been around for months)?&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Queen&#39;s Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8415806&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs &amp; Barriers left behind by Contractor</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8415806</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 17:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.895007 -2.09456</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Please resurface Harp Hill, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8415751</link>
<description>There are multiple potholes which have opened up again after wet weather despite your patching efforts. Please pay Harp Hill the attention it deserves, close it and resurface this entire section properly before there is an accident.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Harp Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8415751&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8415751</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 17:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.898817 -2.046779</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A pothole in road problem, 13th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8415540</link>
<description>Report of pothole: customer reporting same pothole is a recurring issue within same stretch of road.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8415540&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8415540</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.870623 -2.095702</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>