<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Big pothole, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8255131</link>
<description>Big bang as we drove over it - could not avoid because of other traffic&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Crickley Hill, Birdlip, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8255131&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Pothole (NH)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8255131</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 16:35:17 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.843151 -2.096013</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The speed activated sign is broken, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8255013</link>
<description>The speed activated sign near the bus stop and chicane on Gloucester Rd, Andoversford, is broken and not showing anything.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Old Gloucester Road, Andoversford, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8255013&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8255013</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 16:00:20 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.872309 -1.970206</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Outside 48 Gretton Road, Winchcombe, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254798</link>
<description>The drain outside 48 Gretton Road is full of debris. This is the drain at the lowest point of the road and feeds into the culvert which runs along the property. It needs to be completely flushed to allow the drainage point to be maintained.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Gretton Road, Winchcombe, Winchcombe&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254798&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254798</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 14:56:32 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.959004 -1.968487</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bush, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254614</link>
<description>Huge bush has dried out and hanging over parking spot and the road&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8254614.0.jpeg?a1c149d7&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 15, Russell Place, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254614&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Parks/landscapes</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254614</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 14:00:49 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.907313 -2.086708</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Red Cross graffiti on mini roundabout, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254590</link>
<description>There should not be a Red Cross on a mini roundabout&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Green Lane, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254590&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254590</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 13:54:08 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.874855 -2.170348</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree overhanging public footpath to recreation field and Scout Headquarters roof, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254426</link>
<description>Footpath to public field located off Larkhay Road (to the side of Scout Headquarters on Deer Park Road). The tree has been overhanging for 6 months. The Scout group are extremely concerned as this is overhanging their new roof that was replaced 2 years ago.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8254426.0.jpeg?2443f8d2&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Deer Park Road, Hucclecote, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254426&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Fallen tree or branches</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254426</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 13:08:08 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.861555 -2.187272</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Graffiti on Bus Shelter, 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254163</link>
<description>Graffiti has been sprayed over the bus shelter&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8254163.0.jpeg?ea514ea4&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Arle Road, Marle Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254163&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8254163</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 12:11:54 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.903747 -2.092427</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Push buttons at pedestrian crossing outside Morrisons not working on one side of the road., 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253971</link>
<description>Outside morrisons supermarket.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Up Hatherley Way, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253971&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Crossing push buttons not working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253971</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 11:19:37 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.878541 -2.106072</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Leaning over silver birch tree (routine inspection needed), 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253898</link>
<description>Outside 3 Willersey Road&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 3, Willersey Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253898&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253898</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 10:58:23 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.892265 -2.116893</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Multiple graffiti on a utility box and a fence nearby., 5th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253804</link>
<description>On the utility box adjacent to 26 Barley Road and on the fence nearby.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8253804.0.jpeg?df72d9d5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 26, Barley Road, Lynworth, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253804&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253804</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 10:32:35 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.910897 -2.054806</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>There are several street lights not working in the GL51 6HT area. It is obviously very dark in the local area and is a concern for local residents., 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253035</link>
<description>In the general area of the slip road feeding the properties along Hatherley Road in the region of 321 and upwards.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hatherley Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253035&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253035</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:03:21 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.886015 -2.119928</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>There are several street lights not working in the GL51 6HT area. It is obviously very dark in the local area and is a concern for local residents., 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253034</link>
<description>In the general area of the slip road feeding the properties along Hatherley Road in the region of 321 and upwards.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hatherley Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253034&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8253034</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:03:19 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.886015 -2.119928</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A car was parked on the very edge of the start of the yellow lines, however we were still forced to go on the opposite side of the island as would not have fit through, in an average size vehicle, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252979</link>
<description>Barley Road where the island meet the double yellow lines too soon!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Barley Road, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252979&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Line issue (Parking)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252979</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:33:09 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913969 -2.057597</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Yellow lines stop too close to pedestrian island meaning cars and emergency services cannot pass without going the other side of the road, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252975</link>
<description>The start of Barley road as you turn off New Barn Land&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Barley Road, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252975&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road markings, lines and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252975</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 19:32:24 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913969 -2.057597</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apparently abandoned vehicle, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252860</link>
<description>That is a vehicle. Apparently abandoned at the far end of Old Reddings Road, Cheltenham, where it becomes the path alongside the park (sometimes known as the &amp;quot;Humpty dumps&amp;quot;). Reg OY58 BFJ, dark Volvo estate. It has been there about a week so I wondered if abandoned or stolen and dumped.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8252860.0.jpeg?caa9d890&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Old Reddings Road, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252860&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicles</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252860</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 18:31:28 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.887577 -2.12606</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Door 39, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252697</link>
<description>Look at the state they leave in front of the fence. Who’s fault if break down the fence? So who street link, the Council, Road Worker. Working for? Just fixing the street without no incomes, go to the supermarket without no money, where does the refuse truck gets paid. If carry the rubbish to dump. Take receipt who pay? Now who take the risk an allowed government boundary not be clear. None as Landlord resident reported if it is Street Sweeper meant to sweep outside their gate&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please this is an serious matter i wrote my full life story call the emergency felt sorry from 2020. Now wants me to Starve not giving no jobs. Testing if attempted suffer cold Starving they find spite have the purpose to start stealing. No family not giving my compensation in construction but after benefit Claim in my names again use the same method if put under mental health use entitle eligible to find accommodation an put you on benefit. Why they do not help with jobs an find accommodation? Why not building work environment instead of businesses supermarket restaurant activity. Why not have accommodation cheat as shelter prison room.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Why after Mental health to give free Benefit Claim. Look in all the homeless Centre if only allowed strangers in they premises giving away free food an putting them on benefit using needs to find accommodation an make government pay for they housing benefit&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8252697.0.jpeg?2a4654a9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 32, Market Street, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252697&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252697</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.904088 -2.085785</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ditch with cables not filled in many months ago, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252513</link>
<description>Green Lane, Little Witcombe, near retirement mobile homes.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8252513.0.jpeg?d950503b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Green Lane, Badgeworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252513&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned materials</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252513</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 18:03:46 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.837349 -2.129029</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cycle path closed/cyclists dismount here signs - but cycle lane clearly open, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252485</link>
<description>Signs placed closing the cycle lane and advising cyclists to dismount. I chose to use the road as requested and was subject to abuse by motorists along this section. Could the signs be removed or swapped for ‘cyclists rejoin carriageway’ if the cycle lane is clear please.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8252485.0.jpeg?938e8ba8&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cheltenham Road East, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252485&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs &amp; Barriers left behind by Contractor</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252485</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:52:41 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.897004 -2.174411</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree branch broken and hanging over Beeches playground, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252373</link>
<description>A large branch has snapped and remained stuck in the tree. It&amp;#39;s in the playground at the Beeches in Charlton Kings. It&amp;#39;s overhanging and could fall into the playground.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8252373.0.jpeg?1448cfa9&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Sappercombe Lane, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252373&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252373</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:19:18 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.880044 -2.049243</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Request for Extension of Yellow Line Markings to Improve Safety and Emergency Access, 4th October</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252336</link>
<description>Top of barley road, the first island, near new barn lane. This has been an ongoing issue since the yellow lines were painted on earlier this year.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I am writing to raise a safety concern regarding the current layout of road markings near [insert specific location or junction name]. The existing yellow lines terminate too early before the traffic island, which results in vehicles being forced to bypass the island on the wrong side of the road. This creates a significant hazard and obstructs the passage of emergency vehicles, which would otherwise have to mount or cross the island to proceed — posing risks to both the vehicle and road users. According to the Traffic Signs Regulations and General Directions (TSRGD) 2016, yellow line restrictions (no waiting or no loading) must be positioned so that they clearly convey the extent of the restriction and maintain safe, unobstructed access for traffic. In this instance, the current termination point does not adequately prevent obstruction nor ensure a clear passage for emergency response vehicles, as required under Section 130 of the Highways Act 1980, which places a duty on highway authorities to assert and protect the rights of the public to the use and enjoyment of the highway. I respectfully request that the double yellow lines be extended beyond the island to ensure: Vehicles can remain fully on the correct side of the carriageway; Emergency vehicles can pass safely without mounting kerbs or traffic islands; and Compliance with visibility and obstruction standards as set out in the Design Manual for Roads and Bridges (DMRB), CD 169 – Traffic Signs and Road Markings. I would appreciate an inspection of the site and a confirmation that this matter will be reviewed under the authority’s road safety and maintenance obligations. Thank you for your attention to this issue again. I look forward to your response.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8252336.0.jpeg?7356696b&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Barley Road, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252336&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Line issue (Parking)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8252336</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:10:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.913969 -2.057597</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>