<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<atom:link href="https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
<title>Caravan left abandoned, 12th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8408122</link>
<description>Owner of this caravan lived in the flats they either passed away or were evicted. It has been there for months and needs to be removed.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Wilkes Avenue, Hucclecote, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8408122&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Abandoned vehicle</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8408122</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 10:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.859381 -2.188246</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rotten wood and dropped slabs, 12th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407917</link>
<description>A member of the council works team came to fix some dropped slabs but was unable to do so due to a wooden plank being there. A plastic partition was installed and left 2 weeks ago.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8407917.0.jpeg?e8fb6b57&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 65, Union Street, Ewens Farm, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407917&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Missing/broken/rocking/unstable slab</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407917</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 10:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.902443 -2.06714</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>School flashing lights to slow down broken/non illuminating, 12th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407789</link>
<description>Malleson road, just down from the school, on the right-hand side of the road if you were approaching the school from the centre of gotherington. Lights should flash at school hours to get cars to slow down.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 19, Gretton Road, Gotherington, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407789&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Sign plate is missing (Non illuminating sign)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407789</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 10:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.964397 -2.051261</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cones left in the verge, 12th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407751</link>
<description>North verge of the road&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Gloucester Road, Cotswold&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407751&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Signs &amp; Barriers left behind by Contractor</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407751</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 09:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.865373 -2.008336</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gully full of vegetation that is then blocking the run off drain front the new cycle bath, 12th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407730</link>
<description>Outside 85 Cheltenham Road East in front of driveway … have tried clearing the small drain but can not remove the covers for the soak aways that were put in as part of cycle lane scheme, now full of vegetation that needs removing otherwise will further block drainage. I’ve had to put my hand down the drain this morning to pull silt out due to amount of water running into driveway.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cheltenham Road East, Churchdown, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407730&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407730</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 09:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.891875 -2.182073</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ongoing Neglect of Elmfield Avenue and Elmfield Street, 12th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407651</link>
<description>I’ve been reporting the same issue for two years now, and it’s clear that giving more time won’t change anything. As shown in the attached photos, the street has been in poor condition since at least 2009 — something that can easily be verified through Google Maps imagery — although it’s very likely it has been this way for even longer. Sixteen years is quite unacceptable.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Last year, after numerous complaints on this platform (more than ten), a small section of the street was finally repaired. However, both Elmfield Avenue and Elmfield Street remain in a severe state of neglect. There are potholes throughout, growing larger each time, and in this year’s 2025 photo — next to the maroon car — you can clearly see that the ground is sinking, creating a large puddle every time it rains.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The pavements are also in very poor condition: cracked, uneven, and full of holes. I intend to continue reporting these issues regularly until appropriate maintenance work is carried out. Sixteen years without proper repairs is more than enough.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8407651.0.jpeg?82e1c443&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1a, Elmfield Avenue, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407651&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407651</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 09:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.910638 -2.08661</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Drains blocked yet again., 12th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407602</link>
<description>This time the water is so high it is over the footpath and children are having to walk through it on their way into school. The leaves which were along the edge of the road are no longer there. My suspicion is that the leaves have not been cleared away but have been washed into the drains causing the blockage. Council, please don&amp;#39;t email me asking if the problem has gone away on its own this time, just get a truck out asap. It also might be cheaper for you to send a road sweeper out frequently during leaf fall rather than the drain cleaner, just a suggestion.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Church Road, Kingsditch, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407602&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407602</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 09:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.9236 -2.090552</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Huge potholes over 80mm deep in front of Beverston House on Leckhamtpon Lane, 12th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407346</link>
<description>Yesterday 11.11.2025 I was driving on Leckhampton Lane in Cheltenham around 19:00, being dark outside and a car coming from opposite way I hit a huge pothole in the road, Instantly felt some noise in the steering wheel and two warning lights came on the dashboard, stopped about 150m away from the pothole in front of a house sign called Linacre, and start videoing going back to see what I&amp;#39;ve hit. I was surprised to see how big the pothole in road was, very dangerous. I&amp;#39;ve took photos and a video as well and moved on slowly with hazard lights to the next layby. My car now is off road as is not driveable, not sure yet what is the issue, but I will take it to a garage today. I assume i something to do with the steering... The potholes are in front of Beverston House, The house next to Greylands, and they are about 500mm by 500mm wide and over 80mm deep.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Leckhampton Lane, Shurdington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407346&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407346</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 09:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.870576 -2.0957</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>There is NO drain the slope of the road causes water to collect, 12th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407286</link>
<description>At the end of the driveway (47 Cheltenham Road) on corner of Cheltenham Road and Two Hedges Road water collects and cars spray everyone walking along the pavement. This is a route to school for many children and they are often sprayed when we have rain. This problem is ongoing and has been for many years&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8407286.0.jpeg?dd9f9e76&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 7,9, Two Hedges Road, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407286&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8407286</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 08:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.943133 -2.064271</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Blocked drain sub surface, 12th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406944</link>
<description>Blocked, not leaves or on surface&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Barnett Way, Barnwood, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406944&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406944</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 07:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.863043 -2.198214</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Blocked drain causing road flooding, 12th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406932</link>
<description>Corner of Western Roadnear traffic lights. Road badly flooding after rain due to leaves, poor road surface run off angle and blocked drains. Causing pedestrians to be soaked by passing cars.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8406932.0.jpeg?9c76d2ec&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Western Road, Lansdown, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406932&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406932</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 07:38:55 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.901133 -2.086858</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Several deep potholes that keep reopening after repair!!, 12th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406845</link>
<description>Heckler,flanked,perkily- what3words location This location has several deep potholes that need a proper repair !!! This area of road needs a resurface not a bit of tarmac patted into the hole. The repair lasts a few weeks &amp;amp; they reopened. They are deep &amp;amp; doing damage to vehicles !!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Badgeworth Lane, Badgeworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406845&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406845</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 07:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.866413 -2.132236</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The adjacent drain is not blocked but the accumulated rain cannot drain because of road camber. Huge puddle remains and presents a problem for pedestrians, 12th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406643</link>
<description>The flood/ puddle is on corner of Andover Rd and Hatherley St adjacent to 70 Andover Rd. we have reported this on previous occasions and the problem remains. The problem occurs with every episode of moderate to heavy rain. The puddle/ flood only reduces with evaporation as the lie of the road does not allow drainage into any adjacent drain.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8406643.0.jpeg?8527f13f&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 70, Andover Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406643&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406643</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 01:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.892662 -2.08861</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>No street light in Vernon Place, in front of RA Bennet office, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406510</link>
<description>The street lights on Vernon Place have not been functioning for quite some time now. We moved here in September, and since then, we’ve noticed that the lane remains completely dark at night. Earlier, it wasn’t much of an issue because it stayed light until later in the evening, but now it gets dark around 4–5 p.m., making the whole lane &amp;#39;pitch black&amp;#39;.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It feels quite uncomfortable and even a bit fearful to walk through at night. The darkness also encourages unpleasant behaviour, especially over weekends, when people coming out of the nearby Wetherspoon often gather here to smoke, drink, shout, and sometimes urinate on the walls. It’s hardly visible because of how dark it is, but for residents, it feels very unpleasant. Proper lighting would really help improve the safety, comfort, and cleanliness of the area.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8406510.0.jpeg?93059493&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Vernon Place, Fairview, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406510&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street light is permanently out</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406510</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 22:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.897681 -2.072113</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Birdlip House leaking water on to the road, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406457</link>
<description>Dear Gloucestershire Highways, This is the same issue that we had last winter which led to large icy patches on the road close to the school. A significant amount of water is running out of the driveway of Birdlip house then down the Cirencester Road, making it very wet. Last winter when it was below freezing point this same issue caused large areas of the road to become covered in ice. The most significant icy area is in the national speed limit area next to the &amp;quot;chicane&amp;quot; on the exit from the main part of Birdlip village towards Parson&amp;#39;s Pitch. When the temperature goes below freezing this will be very dangerous again this year, we need to get the leak at Birdlip House fixed for good. I appreciate this might not be your jurisdiction but you do have significant influence to bear and can if necessary involve other authorities.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Ermin Way, Birdlip, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406457&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>No rain in 24 hours - water has increased or remained the same</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406457</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 21:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.826896 -2.105178</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Pot hole in road, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406108</link>
<description>Pot hole just before Welcome to Gotherington sign, entering Gotherington.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cleeve Road, Gotherington, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406108&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8406108</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.960527 -2.053988</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Faded double yellow lines, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8405915</link>
<description>From Regents Court Side to the junction of andover road and St Stephens Road people are parking there everyday and causing problems for 94 95&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8405915.0.jpeg?b7c28662&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Saint Stephen&#39;s Road, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8405915&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Line issue (Parking)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8405915</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.892701 -2.090023</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>The drain is blocked problem, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8405514</link>
<description>Blocked Drain Cheltenham GL50 1UF &amp;#10;blocked for over a month . It has been a problem every year and Highways have cleared it in the past . It is a dangerous situation as it creates a bottleneck and a high risk of&amp;#10;collision &#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8405514&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8405514</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.894999 -2.078349</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>TMC - Defects - Other problem, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8405516</link>
<description>remove water from c/way and jet 1x jet gullies and line&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8405516&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>TMC - Defects - Other</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8405516</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.89496831 -2.07816048</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flytipped items, 11th November</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8405246</link>
<description>Large and small items&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8405246.0.jpeg?6f5a7997&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 21, Lansdown Place, Warden Hill, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8405246&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Flytipping</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8405246</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.894242 -2.087574</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>