<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/rss/xsl"?>

<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule"
>

<channel>
<title>New local problems on FixMyStreet</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/?lat=51.897991;lon=-2.071308;d=10</link><uri>https://www.fixmystreet.com/rss/l/51.897991,-2.071308/10</uri>
<description>The latest local problems reported by users</description>
<language>en-gb</language>

<item>
<title>Dangerous Traffic Through Church Street, 4th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8116661</link>
<description>Balcarras School is concerned about the traffic that is being diverted through Church Street as a result of the closure of the A40. A number of our parents have reported near misses with pupils walking to and from the Junior School and the Secondary School.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 54, Church Street, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8116661&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Poor repairs (reinstatement)</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8116661</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:53:33 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.882573 -2.049435</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Timings have changed, 4th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8116651</link>
<description>The timings have changed causing the lights to change too frequently which is causing long tailbacks&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Cheltenham Road East, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8116651&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Green or amber traffic light is not working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8116651</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:48:45 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.900278 -2.159695</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Grafitti on the mini roundabout, 4th September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8116395</link>
<description>The mini roundabout opposite the Tithe Barn in Bishops Cleeve has been vandalised with red paint.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1, Stoke Road, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8116395&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Graffiti</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8116395</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:37:26 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.946533 -2.063981</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Multiple potholes, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8116345</link>
<description>Right hand lane before traffic lights&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Hucclecote Road, Hucclecote, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8116345&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in road</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8116345</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 23:52:42 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.850446 -2.172103</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ratting ironwork outside Rockatech / by bus stop, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115814</link>
<description>Clanks EVERY time a car goes in the direction of Pirton Corner. Has been reported previously over 6 months and nothing has been done. This needs fixing or securing to stop it rattling. It has been marked with spray paint for some considerable times but no work has been done. Please provide an update.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 207, Pirton Lane, Churchdown, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115814&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Loose/rattling cover/ironwork</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115814</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 20:18:51 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.880435 -2.181059</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gridlock traffic and inappropriate vehicles diverting through village. Much too large to do so and causing major traffic issues at all hours of the day. Road by pub and Chinese takeaway is too narrow for both directions of traffic let alone with added diversions, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115813</link>
<description>East end road, round st Mary’s church and all surrounding areas. Happened since London road closure on Monday 1st September due to continue til mid December. This cannot go on for over 3 months it is absolute carnage and somebody will get hurt. I am local resident who has to use this route to get anywhere- I am nearly 40 weeks pregnant and could go into labour at anytime and now have the added stress of not being able to travel anywhere without getting stuck in gridlock traffic!!&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 44A, Church Street, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115813&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Information board identifying emergency contact company/number not displayed</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115813</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 20:18:59 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.882454 -2.049947</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Water not draining away creating large puddle, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115633</link>
<description>The excess water is opposite the entrance to Giles Piece.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8115633.0.jpeg?e2ecda9a&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Langley Road, Winchcombe, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115633&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115633</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:34:25 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.951811 -1.979244</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>After heavy showers, the gutter along the south side of Langdon road is flooded with water to the extent that is is encroaching over pavement where there is a dropped kerb outside no 15, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115282</link>
<description>Drainage along the south kerb of Langdon road, particularly in front of no 15. Water does not drain away and lies along side kerb after heavy rain.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8115282.0.jpeg?eaa77baa&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 25, Langdon Road, Naunton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115282&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115282</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:19:43 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.887024 -2.078488</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Very dangerous situation! We live on Church street, on the one way road around St Mary’s church, in Charlton Kings village. I have seen all day, the chaos that is prevailing in this area, including lorry’s mounting pavements, lorry’s going the wrong way because they are unable to get around the church, due to heavy vehicles and huge traffic using the village local traffic route, instead of the Cirencester Road diversion due to the A40 Charlton kings road works. Three schools are on this route, someone is going to get killed. Please sort better diversion signage, and this needs to be policed., 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115235</link>
<description>At Mary’s Church, Church Street, Charlton Kings (one way road around St Mary’s Church. Route not suitable for large heavy goods vehicles, lorry’s, and should not be used as a diversion due to A40 Charlton kings road closure.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8115235.0.jpeg?467f7141&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 7, Church Street, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115235&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road markings, lines and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115235</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:13:07 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.883144 -2.05295</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Entire road is flooding when the rain is heavy. The drain cant cope and properties, including ours are having there drive ways flooded., 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115201</link>
<description>The Drains outside 105 and 103 Church Road&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8115201.0.jpeg?5c48a9b5&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 103, Church Road, Leckhampton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115201&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115201</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:06:14 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.875368 -2.081898</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Main Drains blocked in open parking space Court Road, number 7, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115163</link>
<description>7, Court Road, Brockworth, Glos, GL3 4EL Outside front door, in the last few days we’ve had excessive rain and flooding in our property garden area, these may be because of these drains or another external source that we are not aware of&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8115163.0.jpeg?71879807&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 1-2, Court Road, Brockworth, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115163&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8115163</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:59:40 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.846929 -2.159174</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Drain blockage, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114987</link>
<description>2A Dinglewell Hucclecote drain blocked&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8114987.0.jpeg?8d694bfb&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Dinglewell, Hucclecote, Gloucester&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114987&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114987</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:21:05 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.855827 -2.193967</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Innsworth lane and rookery road junction zebra crossing missing, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114834</link>
<description>Dear Sir/Madam,&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I am writing to raise a serious safety concern regarding the junction of Innsworth Lane and Rookery Road. This area is used daily by hundreds of children attending Innsworth Junior School, along with parents, carers, and other pedestrians.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;At present, there is no pedestrian crossing facility, such as a zebra crossing, at this busy junction. As a result, children are regularly forced to cross the road while vehicles approach at considerable speed. This creates a highly unsafe environment, particularly during school drop-off and pick-up times when traffic levels are at their highest.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The absence of a designated crossing point poses a significant risk of accidents and injuries. Installing a pedestrian crossing would greatly improve safety, reduce the likelihood of incidents, and provide reassurance to families and residents who use this route daily.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I urge the council to give this matter urgent attention and to consider the installation of a zebra crossing or another appropriate traffic-calming measure at this junction.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Thank you for your time and consideration. I look forward to your response.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Innsworth Lane, Innsworth, Tewkesbury&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114834&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Crossing push buttons not working</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114834</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:52:40 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.888609 -2.207991</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>A40 roadworks/diversion, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114709</link>
<description>Chaos in Charlton Kings village. Proper signage needs to be employed stating &amp;#39;Local Access Only&amp;#39; &amp;amp; &amp;#39;No HGV access&amp;#39; whilst the roadworks are in place on the A40. We are only a matter of days into a potential very long term closure. It is only a matter of time before a serious incident occurs. Cars and lorries mounting pavements to get through. Long queues of traffic through the village. Children are now back to 3 schools in the vicinity.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please please please organise this better... and Police it!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;There has been months of run up to this closure. Diversions and signage have not been thought through adequately.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): Chestnut Terrace, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114709&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>General road markings, lines and stud issues</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114709</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:31:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.882527 -2.052226</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree damaging fence with neighbour, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114615</link>
<description>In my garden behind shed. Neighbour complained to me that their fence is being damaged by it&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8114615.0.jpeg?5eb346bf&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 19, Courtiers Drive, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114615&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114615</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:18:05 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.943844 -2.057287</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tree growing into my property, making mess and not having enough day light., 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114605</link>
<description>On 45 courtiers drive GL528NU&amp;#10;&amp;#10;My neighbour spoken to me aswell and he advised me to file a complaint about the tree that it bothers them aswell.&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8114605.0.jpeg?5db06d1d&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 19, Courtiers Drive, Bishop&#39;s Cleeve&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114605&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Trees</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114605</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:16:26 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.943844 -2.057287</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Blocked drain, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114591</link>
<description>The drain outside number 149 is blocked underneath.&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 147, Brooklyn Road, Wymans Brook, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114591&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>Street cleaning</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114591</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:14:20 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.905983 -2.106527</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Water Level in the drain seems High, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114528</link>
<description>The level of water in the drains seems high, usually when cleaned there is around 121 cm now it is around 40-50 cm and as we have previously had flooding of the road, driveway, footpath and the side of our house could both drains at the bottom of Roxton Drive be cleaned. Both drains out side of number 7 and number 6 if possible to clean may help to avoid being flooded again. Thanks Keith&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 7, Roxton Drive, Hatherley, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114528&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is blocked</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114528</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:10:51 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.890287 -2.1315</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Flooded road, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114453</link>
<description>This was supposed to have been sorted in March but the road is flooded again, the drains are blocked and need to be cleared. After that the real problem needs to be sorted as brought up before ref 11476403&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 54, Cheltenham Road, Winchcombe, Winchcombe&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114453&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>The drain is damaged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114453</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:57:04 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.948748 -1.974925</georss:point>
</item>
<item>
<title>Paving slab sticking up, 3rd September</title>
<link>https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114425</link>
<description>A real hazard for anyone particularly those with restricted eyesight or mobility&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.fixmystreet.com/photo/8114425.0.jpeg?df62c664&quot;&gt;&#10;&lt;br&gt;Nearest road to the pin placed on the map (automatically generated by OpenStreetMap): 11, Pilley Lane, Leckhampton, Cheltenham&#10;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114425&#39;&gt;Report on FixMyStreet&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<category>A pothole in pavement</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.fixmystreet.com/report/8114425</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:53:11 +0100</pubDate>
<georss:point>51.876959 -2.075097</georss:point>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>